[music]
Heat. Heat. [music]
Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Hey,
[music]
>> Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Uh hello everyone.
Am I audible? I hope I am audable.
Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello. [clears throat]
How's everyone doing? Hello.
Oh, one second. Uh,
I'm having the [clears throat] day I
returned back to streaming after my
vacation. I started to get like stupid
amount of uh errors in my back end. And
I'm like, "Bro, what the heck?
[laughter]
I've been uh doing so many
[clears throat] I've been doing so many
uh
private uh unlisted streams and testing
everything. So, every thing is working
and
everything was a lie."
[laughter]
Crazy, man. It's just crazy. But yeah,
how's everyone doing? Hello, welcome.
Wait, [clears throat] let me double
check some stuff. One second.
Yeah, today we uh I we doing like uh
uh today we doing like a uh gorilla
stream. It's an unplanned stream. If you
don't know what gorilla is, it's an
unplanned stream.
Um
yeah, I just came back from my vacation
and I'm back. So, I just wanted to like
um chill with you guys for a bit and
then uh probably we'll be record live
recording a YouTube video. We'll be
doing that before I sleep. Yep.
Uh we'll be doing that before I sleep
and wrap up for today. Uh, yep.
What else I have planned? Yeah, rest of
the stuff are all video content on
YouTube. Uh,
have planned for this month.
Yeah, I only have one month left, right?
Uh, am I lagging? Oh my god.
[clears throat]
Why am I lagging?
Hello, welcome Ki Mind your language on
my menu
language.
No causing out here bro.
What you doing
the language?
Wait, was that on mine?
I pray a lot to hear again and use and
the world [laughter]
wait
oh yeah you're actually on main channel
okay okay
follow the rules got to follow the rules
I got to be more stricter and all
hello
myio [clears throat]
was all one
This is a new version of VC. Okay, let
me just install this update.
Yeah, my V channel was running if I'm
correct. No.
What about my feelings? What about my
Wait.
Oh my god.
It's okay. I'm here. You can talk to me
now. [laughter]
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh my god, my throat.
One second. Uh, you know, uh, give me a
bit. I'll, uh, I'll just, uh, recharge
and, uh, talk, uh, for a bit while I
multitask some stuff which is breaking
in my P. Oh god, what this is?
I thought everything was running well.
Yeah, it's always the time when you uh
come back to do your usual thing,
everything breaks suddenly [laughter]
crazy, isn't it?
And I didn't even uh prepare my OBS for
recording. Apparently, there's a new uh
multi- track video method you can do. Um
I wanted to test that out.
[clears throat]
Uh yeah, you know, uh while I was uh
away from my PC, I was like remote
controlling the PCs so I can like check
up on my board channel that always
channel stuff and I have to do my uh
dailies, right? [laughter]
Blue protocol dailies. So I've been uh
remote controlling my PC and like doing
my dailies and everything.
Thank god there was no power cut for
four days.
Where have you been? I've been on
vacation. Vacation was good. Spend I
spend time with family. It was really
fun. Enjoyed it.
I spent time with family.
Yeah.
Yeah. That was really fun though.
Since um as I mentioned in my YouTube uh
community post, if you haven't checked
it, feel free to check it. Um
yeah, uh this will be my last time I get
to uh hang out with my family. Enjoy,
enjoyed,
enjoyed.
Uh, I posted some images um of uh the
birds and stuff I took pictures of for
some odd reason. [laughter]
Uh, I guess specific places like beach
one or something. It was like um
[clears throat]
uh I visited a few churches. Um, I
visited a few churches. Uh, what is
this? What the heck on? Yeah, I visited
a few churches and
um, beach. Did I post a picture of a
beach? I don't know. Uh, beach. Yeah,
there was a lighthouse and stuff.
Uh, then what else was there?
What else? What else?
last time. Why? Oh, cuz I'm going I'm
I'm going abroad, right? Uh after next
month, April.
Yeah. So, last time I only I get to
spend two months in India and then I'm
then I'm
in a different country. Yeah.
So, uh I can't I can't specifically say
where did I went, but yeah, it was a
good time. My uh cousins were there, so
I
hang out with cousins,
cousin uncle and Andy and my family.
Yeah. Oh my god. Where you going? Uh I'm
going to Japan.
I I thought uh I
the last time you came by, we talked
about this. Did you forget?
Last time you came by,
there's a time for it. Uh April, April
1, I'll be there. Yeah. Um so I have
like February and March mid uh end of
March time. Yeah. Yeah. So before I
prepare to go
uh
going to take like a year or so. No, no,
no, no, no. I'm going this year
probably. Not sure. It's not confirmed
yet. I'll get confirmation by next week.
Yeah, next week. Uh next week or 16th
I'll get to know my confirmation.
Uh
yeah, I hope everything goes well. I'm
excited.
So, no stream anymore. I'll try to
stream more more I'll do more video
content not on YouTube. I'll try to do
more video content on YouTube like a
vlog or something. I haven't tried
vlogging. Uh so, I'll see how that goes.
Uh
uh but uh streaming can only be possible
once I um once I um how do I say
streaming uh can be only possible once I
uh get everything sorted out like
internet connection laptop got to buy a
new laptop internet connection
uh don't I don't even know if I'll have
an environment so I can be like a
private space now so I can like have my
I can do stuff.
No, no, not for years. Basically 6
months at least maybe there might be no
stream 6 months till I uh move out get
my own place.
Uh yeah, cuz I don't know dormatory
rules. I'll be in a dorm. I'll have
roommates and stuff. Uh
God knows how things will be.
So yeah,
I can't expect or predict anything.
Going to stay. No, I'm going for
language studies. A language. Language.
master stuff going to be uh
28.
Yep. Student exchange. Yep. Yep.
Language exchange. Foreign exchange
student I guess. Going to a different
country to learn the language so we can
do two year uh language studies will be
for two years.
So
yeah, I guess will be my might before
like two years. Yep.
It's unpredictable. I don't know how
things will be but
are you like on scholar? No, no, no, no.
Not scholarship or anything like that.
Nope. Nope. Nope.
I wish [laughter]
I would I would love to have like a
scholarship or something. I I would love
to, man.
[laughter]
I would wish for that. Yeah,
it's going to cost a lot. Yeah, I would.
Uh,
bro, why the heck is this struggling to
I can't even announce that I'm live on
live live on YouTube on Discord. Bro,
what the heck is wrong going wrong?
What?
Where did I make a mistake? So, where
you going? I'm going for my future
stuff.
going to go there and study the
language.
Uh do university degree stuff and get a
job and stuff. Settle there
and stuff. Yeah. [clears throat] No, I
know. I'm just going to go there. Going
abro and stuff.
Okay. Uh f uh [sighs and gasps]
PC. Come on, listen to me. Let me make
you work so I can start my start my
stream. No, I always start my What am I
saying? I almost started my my stream.
[laughter]
No, I always start my What am I saying?
How much
tea on YouTube?
Almost
there.
I can't
challenge every
challenge.
Wait,
wait, wait. Wait, wait. You hear that?
>> Wait. You hear that? Oh my god. What the
heck?
Wait,
I fixed it. Ah, I'm not using obvious. I
uh haven't opened this setup.
uh in a while. That's why. That's why.
Oh,
I was routing my browser. What?
Crazy. Oh, okay. No, no. I uh opened my
stream, YouTube stream. That's why you
heard like u double uh Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Um I forgot to cut the audio from for my
browser.
So that's why you heard like the browser
audio for a second. My bad. My bad.
Uh
hundreds.
Hundreds.
Okay.
to this.
Okay, this is correct.
I want to show my screen, but I hope
it's not too technical cuz there's so
much. I have to make a tutorial, too.
No. So, so I have to like make it
prettier.
God, so much work. Wow.
I just came back though.
[gasps] so much work. Okay, let me make
the announcement that I'm live.
I have to do I forgot to do the
Instagram story.
Oh boy, boy.
I missed the streaming.
It's like you forgot how things are.
[laughter]
How you have to do every single thing?
Uh you need which specific
specialization? Music. Uh probably going
to do music. So
probably going to do music or
literature. Not sure.
Depends what opportunity opens up for
me. I I do have uh backup plans. I I I'm
learning this thing.
I am really bad at singing but I'm
learning to sing.
Uh
and uh I like to do uh like music
production like use a software to
digitally make music. No, I like to do
that.
Um, I think I'm since I haven't touched
it for a while, I'm basically a
practically a beginner.
Practically a beginner.
Okay, announcement is done. Okay, good,
good, good.
Finally.
Uh, you know, I can't I can't I know
basic Japanese. Don't worry about it.
Hopes
things will work out. Don't worry too
much.
Yeah.
And and I uh recently uh
how come your parents agreed for it
then? If my parents didn't agree for it,
then why am I even going there in the
first place? You know,
see family agreed, they know everything.
Uh what what to expect, what not to
expect, everything, how much the
expenses, everything.
So yeah.
Uh
why they agreed? Think about it, Kaki.
like uh
you you want to study abroad, you go uh
you have an interest in whatever you
want to do. Even if you're going abroad
or staying in your own country or
something, you have an interest, you
have a uh this and that you wish to do.
Uh
and you are you feel like you're
confident enough to go for it.
you go for it. No, if your family
situation is okay and family allows it,
you will go for it, right? Like just
like that.
Most of my classmates I knew from my
high school days and college days. All
of them are most of them are like some
settled here, some are abroad
like that.
And the situation went wrong.
H hello ferocious welcome. How you
doing? How are you? How are you?
How's life? Whatever situation went
wrong. Hello D. I know you. Don't worry.
Did you change your name? What does
gorilla refer in the title of the
stream? By the way, gorilla means
um
gorilla means an unplanned, unorganized,
unplanned, unexpected stream.
I bet they didn't left just in hope. You
don't even have a plan. I have a plan. I
already explained to my uh to to my
stream like uh five, six, seven times.
And I feel like that was the biggest
mistake cuz um you know uh the the day I
started to open up about my personal
life stuff
uh I'm starting to get two sides of
people. One is the supportive side and
other is the uh worrying side.
So I don't know man normally people
don't share
um stuff they do in their private life
now. Yeah I think I made that mistake
but it's okay I we learned from our
mistakes now but yeah hello welcome.
It's been a while. How is life?
Good evening.
Congratulations. Wait for what? by
because I also started streaming and
making videos. Oh, good, good, good.
Let's go.
How are you? I'm doing great. Just came
back home today after like vacation.
Well, I'm sure you're on the woring
side. Yeah, don't worry. I'm also
worrying about my stuff. Now,
see, I'm not alone. No even if I'm going
to a country with where I don't have
anyone to protect me and save me and
stuff how I have in my own place right
and my family is there uh people friends
are there cousins are there everyone is
there you know um but I won't be alone I
I made I made uh good friends not
Japanese people like Indian people and
like and people I trust if if anything
happens anything I'm lost or confused
anything I can reach out to them and
everything and yeah you go classmates uh
Japanese school classmates who are also
going to the same school so I'm not
alone no [snorts] I'm sad not good don't
worry
yeah
don't worry Aditi I I'm going to be here
till March mid mid March.
So yeah, don't worry. I will I'll be
doing streams and this time this time
I'm not doing a Sabbathon.
There won't be Joathon. That's all.
Yeah.
You know, the reason why people
uh people uh feel like they'll miss me
and stuff. No, that's why I made the
that 24x7 channel and stuff.
Yeah.
I I'm going to record a video regarding
that right now after a bit. Let me fix
this stupid bug I'm having. Um from your
school uh langu language local language
institutions.
Yeah. So I'm not alone. No.
Uh two reasons. First my best friend is
also in IR also in IR going to miss her.
Second you're also going to gone soon.
Yeah. Don't worry. I'm going to be here.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Classmates are there. Don't
worry. Uh uh there's like um I think uh
my language school uh there will be
three four people.
Total of 12 12 parents are going. Uh
some people are going to different
different states. Uh I'm going to a
different state, a specific school. They
are going to a different state and a
specific school. like that.
[sighs]
Uh best friend, my lover of my life. A
yeah, I know that moment
my uh childhood friends now they all
left me though left me as in uh
um one went to
one man went to like
what's the country's name? God, what's
the name? Ireland. Yeah. One went to
Ireland.
Reason is immortal. All else is mortal.
To see unicard mathematician
love of life. [laughter]
[snorts]
So what's uh what's everyone been up to?
How was life?
How have been everything?
Tell me. I've been out of the loop.
what's been happening on the internet
recently.
So this how students go abroad by taking
commissions, right? It's more like an
MCN as in they teach the language, they
teach about the cultural stuff and
everything. Then they um provide you
opportunities to take interviews with
other schools
uh within Japan and stuff cuz they have
lingups and tie-ups, right? and
uh yeah and and um after you pass the
interview
um [clears throat]
uh like a requirement for uh to be able
to attend a language school in Japan,
it's like you need uh some sort of hours
like I think um 300 hours of learning a
lang
Japanese language level within a local
institute that certificate plus
uh passing certificate of the level. For
example, like for me, I passed N5 NLP
N5, right? So that minimum requirement
is N5 N4 better. Then what else? Yeah, I
like that. So they [clears throat] uh
give you an opportunity they um connect
with you with the language. Cool. You
pass the interview and everything and
then
till you are admitted there as in you
are sent over there the flight ticket
everything comes in a package. They uh
the local institute uh helps you with
that local uh document translation stuff
everything the local institute does it.
Then uh once you're in Japan, the
language school
uh yeah the langu Japanese language
school they
uh like uh the local institute will be
like your guardian in your way cuz if
anything happens like say you are 5
minutes late or 1 minute late for your
morning classes uh while in Japan right
the
uh the principal will just phone your
in-law local institute like your
guardian like the people right they'll
call do a meeting uh and you have to
write an essay or apology letter they
have to write an apology letter on your
behalf till you get a part-time job
till you get a part-time job until
you're stable stable the local institute
um is uh like uh has to take care of you
and has like has to look after
everything uh of the Yeah. So literally
they will look after the students no
matter what that kind of thing. Then
after uh graduating from the language
school then it's up to you. No you uh
you leave your own path like do
university or find a job or something.
It's on you right and uh yeah like that.
I don't like that.
Okay. Where am I? Where am I? Where am
I?
No major change. Are we watching too
much math related videos which are too
out of syllables? That's new. Oh yeah,
some people are having board exams. No.
Are you having board exams? Anyone in my
chat?
YouTube Twitchk. Anyone? Uh, who's here?
Anyone of you having board exams
link
okay wait I have to log in what
have you listened to good
incompleteness theorem nope what is that
what is that What?
Ha.
I'm in 11th grade. No board. No, you're
going to have board.
No. Oh, yeah. Yeah. You don't have
board. Yeah. Yeah. 12th. Yeah. 12th.
You'll have board. Yeah. I forgot.
Sorry. Good luck. Good luck. Don't slack
off.
Some colleagues I
are having their boards
exam season now cuz it's already
February no
February March
even if it was I have already studied
the whole syllabus of 12th long ago.
Wow. Which sy which syllabus ICE or I
CBSC or state or which syllabus are you?
Damn.
I I remember uh when I was studying in
IC
that time my CBSC friends were like I
think fifth no
uh seventh grade people were learning
like ninth CBSC ninth grade uh content
like syllabus contents and stuff.
I'm preparing for G e J E G I think I
told you wrong. Oh yes yes yes yes. He
told me during the
uh when was it was I think I was playing
ar uh not arids um
aratus that time [cough]
or or was it the time you told me to
react to Genchin Impact video or
something? No you I remember one time
you told me like jock look at this.
Yeah. Yeah. that around that time,
right? Yeah.
Nice. Nice.
Okay. [sighs and gasps]
Thank you for the hydrate.
I'm getting some water. I'm really
having like a throat pain today.
Don't know why.
[clears throat]
But yeah, I did a checkup, full body
checkup,
and the doctor said I'm all right. I'm
okay and stuff cuz no, I I have this
dust allergy issue. I keep sneezing and
sneezing and sneezing so much.
It is pain.
102. What is this?
N there. What is this
one?
Bro, I honestly, you know, I was like,
I'm going to record my video stuff
and uh call it a day.
You're old. You shouldn't go outside in
this. Why do you mean old? Oh, I am not
old. I'm still young. O,
no.
I saw your chat. You You said on the
board the the the
always on channel. You brat. Did you
just call me uncle again? Oh my god.
Hello Nathan. Oh my god. How are you?
How are you? How are you? Hello.
Been forever. How is life Nathan? Hello.
Uh although I have only completed maths
fully about
physics 12. It's 515 20%. Oh, it's been
a bit. How was vacation? Vacation was
good.
I spend time with family.
I needed like a family time. It was
good. Enjoyed it.
Yeah. I think I need to keep those
photos and everything um saved
somewhere.
My phone storage is full. Full.
My phone storage is full. Bro, I need a
I need a I bought like a memory card
today. I I ordered it while I was
returning back home.
Um
uh it was like a 256 GB memory card from
SanDisk. My phone storage internal
storage is 128 now. And I was like,
"Okay, I'll stop getting the error
message like no device storage once I
insert my memory, the new memory card."
And I was like,
"Yeah, no more this thing." But I was so
wrong. all these apps. No, like I I
whenever I see some like applications on
like play store, I just randomly install
it or I'll be like, "Oh, I can use this
for something something and I'll forget
about it." Then uh when the time comes
where I feel like I have to clear up
some storage and in uninstall these
applications
um then I'm like ah do I need to
[snorts]
you must click to uh to know I don't
take pictures of myself I take pictures
of like my environment like buildings
birds this and that
just so you know I might be one of the
old god. Yes, Nathan is an old viewer.
Yes, Nathan is an old concert plate.
Nathan has been dian
let me think 2022
am I right? Uh wait 2022 right? Uh, like
No, wait, wait, wait. Wait, wait, hold
up. No, no, no, wait.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. 20 22 21 2022. Yeah.
I was in the art forest then. Yes.
Sure.
Yeah.
Uh
it's been such a long time. Five years.
Yeah. You know, I got some exciting news
coming soon
and I'm still thinking if I should
reveal it this month or next month.
I have to uh I have to reach out to two
more people to finalize everything.
Um
yeah. Exc. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You see the goal up on the top
like make Joik's new model and stuff.
Yeah. I I finally
finally
got
I don't know if I should say it, but
uh not the model. The model is not
ready, but I I um got my IP.
I paid for it. I paid for the uh for
this year. Yeah.
If you watch my YouTube video about my
why my mortal situation changed video,
you'll understand.
So, um till there I uh um I'm I got my
IP stuff.
So, uh so I'm planning to uh reveal the
model PNG.
It's like um
it's like there's this saying no you
make it exist first and improve
on it later right like Hightail and
stuff right hightail recently got
released they're going to make it exist
and slowly slowly slowly make it better
now so I'm going to follow the same
tactic so it's not going to be like your
traditional YouTuber debuted where they
I'll have a live 2D model and stuff. Um,
it's going to be a different a little
bit different. It's more like I'm going
to be revealing the model of the live
the model art for the live 2D model and
it'll be PNG like how we are doing PNG.
I'll do that and then once we have
proper enough money uh I'll get the
rigging done in the future. Yeah.
Yeah. So, it's going to be the proper
do.
Yeah. Let's go.
But yeah, I'm still worried about a lot
of things, man.
Uh and uh this is going to be Jocknik's
proper. Yes. Yes. The official design
for Jockn and the feature.
Yeah.
God, it's BTing is expensive, man.
Honestly, it's like a expensive hobby.
Yeah, crazy. [laughter]
Oh my god, I'm I'm super excited about
it.
I'm really excited for that. I hope
everything goes well.
Okay, let me fix this bug and we'll how
rich I'm not rich. See, if I was rich, I
wouldn't be having a goal on stream
though.
Saying like I need money for my model
and stuff. Nope. $2,000 is like how much
in uh Indian rupees? It's like you can
buy a new
uh as um
what's the brand again? Uh you can buy
like a 5090 or 5080 laptop like um Asus
ROG Sticks G16
2025 edition. That's the laptop I'm
looking for. Uh I'll buy a secondhand
version of it if if there's a cheaper
one. Yeah. But yeah, it's like those
expensive gaming laptops. No, it's
around that much, I think.
Yeah. I mean, I had like I even
explained on my YouTube video like um I
could have went with like some
customizable model and stuff, but if you
think about it, I got that opportunity,
you know, to have my own original design
and everything.
uh right and things didn't work out in
the corporate space but still uh I'm
independent now um myself right so even
if that's the side of things did not
work
uh now I have to handle everything
myself and yeah which laptop oh I see
I'm going to get this one um
G16 uh sticks uh S is rogue.
Do you earn salary? Nope. I'm a student.
I I uh I quit my job uh freelance job
um like uh
four months ago,
four, five months ago.
Let me type it in chat.
Yeah, I was earning a bit from that
freelance job thingy.
It was more like management
students part time there if they Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to do part time in
Japan. Yeah. Just because we share
goals, we need doing while poor job.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Hi.
Uh
bro, thing is not thinging. Uhhuh. Uh,
I've been looking at this error for like
a long time. Okay, you know what? I'm
going to switch my screen
for a bit. Uh, I'll prepare for the
YouTube video. So, we're going to record
a video regarding my 24x7 channel. Uh,
why I made it and the why I made it
video. That's it's going to be two
videos. One uh less than five minute
video. It's it's just going to be about
why I made it. And the second part of
the video, it's a different video. That
will be the technical details. That's
going to be a tutorial,
not tutorial, more like giving an
explanation on my implementation on how
I did it. So if there's any people who
are interested, no, they can like um
they can like uh check what I did and
like maybe make it better. I don't know.
Just like um it's going to be like a
small technical details.
Hi. Okay, let me just uh arrange
everything so I can like
uh do stuff. One second.
So for the technical details, I'll have
these three buttons
sync and activ
everything my all my social media
everything is jocknick.
I think you can do insta and it will
show up. No, IG.
Oh, yeah. There you go. See the errors?
I'm trying to fix it. It's not working,
man.
Uh,
okay. One second. Now I have to
turn this guy off. This guy is annoying.
But it is off. Then who is running it?
What?
What is this?
392.
392. What the heck? Who?
3 92. 392. Okay, one second.
Uh
3 92 this code back end. What is this?
Who? Oh my god.
kill all of this.
Ah, this guy. Ah,
you were making an issue right here. Oh
my god. Okay. [clears throat]
Uh,
oh yeah. Yeah. Before I make the video,
um, just going to do a trial run. Okay.
Uh, where is notion?
Notion.
So this is how my channel runs.
So as you can see uh these are all the
YouTube playlist
literally uh
everything you see on my YouTube channel
all the playlist
all the public ones all of them.
So I have to explain it like that. No.
Okay. I have to explain like Yeah. So
these uh playlist get uh get
automatically added over here and I have
to
Yeah. I just have to just
uh let it run. That's it.
So today is what? Today is
Wednesday.
So So the war cycle changes every
Saturday. So that means um
currently uh Destiny 2, Splitgate,
what else? And piano learning and uh
freak. Okay.
Uh
so
Battlefield Destiny 2. Okay. Battlefield
Destiny 2 piano learning. So every
Saturday three playlist will be active.
It will be randomized. H and uh so once
uh these playlists are taken it will be
removed from the cycle. How many songs
you have on YouTube? I think 1k one one
one,
100 something.
I realized that I hit 1k last year and
still I haven't done much streams
because I took a break a lot of breaks.
That's a lot to organize. Yeah. Hello
Domo.
Wait, that's a zero or O. Hello, welcome
to the stream. Hello. Hello.
So, uh, so, uh, it's going to
automatically,
uh, do the
playlist.
Oh, there's an update. You know what?
I'll just update it. Okay. So, it's
going to automatically do the playlist.
Uh, this sings it from my YouTube
channel.
Uh, wait, is it allowed to talk about
YouTube DLP? Wait, let me Google this.
Is is it allowed to mention
YT DLP
YouTube DLP on YouTube? Is it
against to
all you really not need to know is
YouTube
no valid no in French users if you use
it to download copyrighted material. Oh
god.
Uh,
so wait, no, I'm downloading my own live
stream. So,
so it's not against TS. No way.
Somebody's saying in the com is my not
in a ban promoting it. Ah,
no. I can't mention it.
Oh, why can't mention it? No.
Okay.
Okay. We have to think of a different
strategy then.
Okay.
Oh god, I can't mention it. No, I can
just show it. No,
one second. Uh, domin.
So, I think I'm just going to That's the
Notion API.
Where is it? Yeah, I'm just going to
copy this and paste it here. I I'll just
show like the result,
right?
Oh, wait. Sorry. Uh wrong
place.
Is it me or my my PC is lagging more and
more
second? Uh
bridge
open in terminal. Okay. Okay. I pasted
here. So I'm just going to show like
uh I don't want to do the API, man.
That's too much.
I don't want to do VPN. Wait, is it
working or is it broken, bro?
No, it's Don't worry. Don't you don't
need to um understand these. It's too
technical though. Yeah, don't worry.
Kaki, I've been lurking for a while
actually. I guess this is my first time
I'm chatting. Oh, thank you for lurking.
It means a lot.
Uh okay. [clears throat]
Uh
so there's two commands I think I can
show.
This is the notion that uh fetch
playlist single. Okay. Okay. This is the
playlist. No wait. Created playlist
active. Wait, wait, wait. Hold up. I
have to explain for the people
like what do I do here? And oh god,
won't they get their head busted like
when they look at all of this?
Should I start scripting?
Uh,
merged. Oh yeah, fall back. I need fall
back. Fall back is basically this. So,
if I go to my website, jok.
Oh, wait. Uh, it's not here. Sorry. Uh,
a void imped playlist. Avoid
darkness
slash
miscellaneous. No, no, no, no. Stream
vidget slash No, wait. What? Wait. What
was the
I need to put a URL for this bro. Uh
YouTube embed Vh [sighs]
embed.
Oh, wait. I have it here. Okay. Okay.
Okay. So, uh I think I can just another
error. I'll fix it later. I don't want
the error to show up when I'm recording.
So basically
um it fetches three playlist at a time
for a week every Saturday. Currently
Battlefield, Destiny 2 and uh piano
learning, right? So piano learning is on
a random state while
yeah Battlefield and Destiny is also
random state. So there sequential and
random. Random means it will look like
this. Uh piano learning playlist only
has one video so it'll show just one.
Then battlefield was the second thing
right. So it will just keep randomized.
It will not be like episode like uh part
one, part two, part three. Sequential is
like numbered random will be randomized.
It won't be the same. No repeat of
streams will be there. And after it uh
reaches the three playlist
stuff, rest will be randomized content.
I put like 90 videos. So this is for
like a one week worth of [snorts]
I mean at least a month worth of thingy
I think uh for the award. So I can I
think I can explain it like that. I
think right.
Uh [sighs]
what else? Uh bro, I'm not prepared.
This is bad. I never do tutorials. It's
too complicated. So yeah, this is how it
will look like. This is all of my videos
I done in my YouTube. So that's like how
many how many uh 1K videos I think. Uh
so all of this is 1,000 video ids every
stream excluding YouTube shots and
videos
uh only live stream past broadcast all
of it is in organized ob uh objects.
Yeah. Yeah. See the formatting. Yeah.
Like that. Okay.
Uh and
uh
what else can I do?
Also, I'm working on something new. Let
me can I show that for a bit? So, uh you
know, this was my dream ever since I got
inspired by this big uh Twitch streamer
called Coilation. You might know him.
He's a big streamer, content creator.
Co. So, uh, Co has this thing now. You
can loging in with your Twitch account
on his website.
Uh, you can log in, uh, to his, uh, to
Yeah, you can loging in with your Twitch
account to his website. Uh, this is like
a forum. Don't mind that. Why we are
looking here is
uh, this one token store. So people uh
view his viewers can gain tokens
from watching his stream and uh
interacting with his content and stuff.
And you can gain tokens and stuff. And
you can uh if you have enough tokens,
you can join like clans and stuff like
uh game clans, right? Like Destiny clan
and stuff and like a lot of things. And
also there's like like um like a
uh thing like a avatar thingy. Where is
it? Where is it? Where is it? Yeah.
Covatas.
Yeah, this thing like a avatar thingy.
You can build your own avatar using the
currency
the tokens you earn from uh
contributing. No, a channel. It's like
Twitch channel points kind of thingy. I
want to do this someday, man.
I want to do this someday. Thank you for
the hydray. Let me drink some water.
So, this inspired me a lot. So, I was
ching talking with Chad GPun
uh and I was making this system called
unified can you say it? Okay. Unified
user map. So, I'll show you the
structure of it I made. Uh where is it?
Uh user map. Okay. So uh
where is user? Okay. So all the people
who are chatting on both my 24x7 channel
and main channel they get uh made into a
user. You get your u uh customizable UI
not customizable you have your internal
UID and uh public UID it's like
if you play games right under the bottom
of the screen you have your uh user ID
right same system you have hello AB
hello Ragnar welcome welcome
so uh so basically uh as you can see
everyone Yes, these are the internal ID.
So for example,
>> [sighs]
>> uh let me think. Yeah, mine. This is
mine. So this is mine. Platforms I'm
adding Billy Billy, Twitch, YouTube,
kick. So four platforms are there. So
this is going to be so one internal ID
is for one platform. I can't merge it
sadly. Uh I had some issues doing the
merging. So I can't merge it. So every
person who chats on either of the four
platforms you will get your public
facing ID and your internal ID and from
that I basically build uh rebuild my set
my the uh I'm going to make the chat log
system more better.
I'm in sensei stream. I wanted to chat
with you too. Ah, it's a cafe.
[laughter]
It's okay. Hello.
So, yeah, kind of like that. And um I
have to work on the link and merge. So,
lingan merge will be like an admin
command. So I have to do exclamation
point uh admin merge and I can link uh
for example um
for example let's take myself uh if I am
chatting on Twitch I can type
exclamation uh admin merge and then I I
do like this
uh let me show you the registry file as
Well, so I have to write like this.
Twitch colon your Twitch ID.
Then I have to write kick semicol uh
this dot dot thingy kick ID. Then
YouTube your YouTube user ID like that.
That's how you merge it.
Yeah. And uh once you merge it, you'll
have your own public UID thingy under
your internal thing. Yeah. It's a bit
complicated. It's bare bones. not good
enough but it kind of works.
Yeah.
Uh and I wanted to make it way better uh
like having like a user same thing like
co has right I thought of having a
system where I can lo like I will have
like a admin login
uh for myself so I don't need to link my
YouTube API kick twitch API stuff for my
Sammy stuff to work I can just use my
website and let it get the token and for
users for you guys. You can log in with
your Discord.
You can loging in with your Discord.
Twitch, YouTube, Kick, all those
platforms. It's like uh
it's like um
how do I say it? It's like uh you know
when you go to your profile, you have
your connected accounts. No, you can
link your accounts. Yeah. So if those
who are h those who have membership on
Twitch and YouTube, you'll get access to
like some
stuff. I think if I can get it to work.
Yeah. Yeah. Like membership content. No,
you can get that.
Yeah. Then I have to think about those
who can't afford membership. I have to
think about them how they can still get
the condens uh which are part of
memberships, right? membership
exclusive. I don't know. I I'll think
about later. But yeah, I got I abandoned
the site track. Sorry. [laughter]
H [sighs] So yeah, Sammy stuff.
He lost me an eternity ago.
Hey, Joa. And yeah, like I made it work.
So like you see, I can have all of your
chat logs here. Like your first message.
I'm going to I have to revamp this. I
have to fix this
from where and how you learned it. I
learned it all myself.
Yeah, it's just too much and uh too much
extra. I feel like you don't need any of
this. I feel like it's something needed.
So, I just do it. [laughter]
God, I have to fix this error, man. Let
me just fix this. Okay, one second. Uh,
so I'm currently live.
So we have to
we have to fix this uh
I have to fix this uh target.
Okay. So I have to fix this uh
huge.
I don't know.
Uh
what is this? Oh yeah, this is the file
which backs up all the YouTube uh
playlist. So as you can see, Counter
Strike, Battle Bet, analyst at Hongkey
Star, Red Shots playlist. I'm not a
programmer. I do not know coding. I just
use this software called Sammy
uh and I learned how to use it. That's
it.
I I think I understood basic coding
through that. That's it. I I don't know
coding at all.
Technical stuff is
how long uh how long you learn by
watching it? Uh honestly speaking, I've
been doing Sammy stuff ever since it got
released like 2021.
It used to be called as Leorin board.
Yeah. The thing is not I'll tell you my
my idea my thing.
So I I'll get this unique idea I want to
do for my streams
and I'll be like okay I want to do this.
How can I do it? I'll just mess around.
It's like you play around with Photoshop
or Adobe Illustrator and stuff. No, like
you tinker around with the software,
right? But when you're confused and
lost, I just went to the support server
of Sammy.
I Yeah, like here I all I like I was
lost with some stuff with the API time
API stuff. So I asked my doubt how can I
fix it? uh people who are supportive who
uh also do the same thing with the
software they'll guide you tell you uh
that you can do this this way or this
way there's multiple ways to do it like
that and another thing uh like a
learning material you can do is other
people who have their issues right you
can just go through their query like oh
this is the problem they are facing and
the helper or the moderator
This is what they suggested and like
that you read through this and try to
replicate it in your own way. Like can I
do this myself? How can I do it like
that? Like if I'm being honest, my
YouTube stuff hap uh YouTube uh V idea
came from this thread. Let me show you.
Uh I think it's over here.
YouTube.
Where is it?
Uh
YouTube.
Where is it?
Oh lord.
Oh, let me find it. BRB.
Huh? Where is that,
bro? Where is it? Uh [clears throat]
uh.
BRB.
Where is it? Wait. YouTube. Hold up.
Wait, wait, wait. YouTube BRV
random YouTube random.
Help. Oh, yeah. Yeah. This one. This
one. This one. This one. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. This guy. This guy.
This guy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. This one. This one. This
one. I think I can mention this in the
video as well.
Uh
God, I have to scroll all the way up.
>> [laughter]
[gasps]
>> So this guy wanted like uh like his
YouTube streams like videos and stuff or
clips to be shown when he's on a BRB
screen. Okay. So I was like randomly one
day like on 2023 I think around this
time I was like uh doing some other
stuff in Sammy and I came across this.
So I was like, "Oh, this is cool."
And I was following this thread on how
to use YouTube API,
how to get the random timestamp,
everything, right? That's how I
initially got inspiration. Then I made
it myself,
which is this
uh if I can find it.
Uh yeah, this is version one.
This was version one. And uh then I
revamped it for the W channel version
three. This is version three. And the
one you see these three with big
buttons. This is version five
which I'll have to make the video about
using notion and stuff. Is my stream
lagging? I can see the lag.
And yeah, my my 24x7 channel is
currently running.
[laughter]
Oh, wait, it's not running. Sorry, I
ended the stream. Wait one second.
So, I use Mel to send it to Twitch,
YouTube, kick,
all those stuff.
I had to explain that. And I use and
this is how the V stuff everything is
here.
Oh, you got time for all of this? I I
spend about uh two hours every day
working and working. Hello again. Uh
again,
he's not studying Japanese. So yes, all
the time.
Hello.
Hello. Hello.
Okay, let me just fix everything and
just uh
wrap up.
I gotta go. I gotta do the video
recording, right? I'm one second. No,
let me just quickly fix it. Uh don't
mind it. You can just chat with me.
Don't mind the screen. You can ignore
the screen. Just listen to my voice and
just chat with me. Uh if you if the
screen is too much technical for you,
don't worry.
Okay. Um
uh today's stream is RX5.
I have to delete this.
Uh [sighs]
no, I think I spent about for this
YouTube button. No. Okay, I'll tell you
the time duration for this. YouTube API
fetch live ongoing fetch upcoming
completed main map stream registry. I
spent 3 months on this. I finished it
last month uh last month around uh 25th
of January.
I finally finished it. The Discord API
stuff is also good. But even if I go
live, even today there are stuff which
are breaking and I hate it every single
time. It's such a annoying thing though.
It is such an annoying thing.
[clears throat]
One second.
Love to do this.
Uh,
take rest.
Take rest.
Take rest. Take rest.
Okay, let me just quickly uh do this
[sighs] uh so I can like speedrun this.
Uh I'm sorry you have to watch me do
this. [laughter]
Normally I would do this off stream, but
that stupid error is getting shown every
single time and I hate it. Uh
don't give me Japanese keyboard. Uh this
one. No. Uh let's search.
How come you're showing error? Oh my
god.
Okay, this is today's stream, right?
Gorilla stream back from vacation. Start
time. Everything is here.
Then how come there's an error?
Okay, this is correct.
Why are you not populating?
Oh my god.
Why are you not populating? Hello.
Why are you empty? Hello.
No.
Delete. Delete.
But
uh oh, you are playing World of
Warcraft. Are you a naughty IRL? I don't
know. I like I like a technological
stuff and everything. It's fun.
Tech stuff is fun. Who doesn't love it?
I don't think I'm nerdy.
I doubt I'm nerdy. [laughter]
Uh, you know, I have to prepare my uh
new model reveal stuff. I haven't even
uh
like thought about how I would want to
do it. Never think
too much.
Uh, so it's going to thing, right?
Oh,
these are upcoming streams.
90s were better.
Now, the thing with me is now I don't
want to take so much steps to do stuff.
If there's a way to automate, I'm going
to do it.
That's why I automated the all of these
stuff cuz I was I hated that I had to go
on Discord and schedule an Discord
event, announce my stream, this and
that, this and that. Too much work. So,
I automated all of this.
Yeah.
all those stuff.
It's kind It's kind of looping. It's not
supposed to loop though.
Why are you laughing?
En you know
that is nice
two streams
866 wait
five six seven eight eight Uh 16 16
I don't know math help. H
uh
is it supposed to be looping all stream?
Ah, it's looping it in a way. I don't
want that.
Hello Alyssa. I see you on Twitch.
Hello. Hello.
Uh
oh. This is that VR chat stream I never
streamed. [laughter]
Oh my god. I never did the stream. Okay,
it's done. Okay, wait. So technically
you should be done fixing it by itself,
right?
No, brother. [laughter] Why?
Wait, did I do something wrong? Wait,
what the heck?
Hold on. Wait a minute.
What the
Why are you not merging it? Let me do
the stream, bro.
Uh, okay. We don't need completed
streams or upcoming streams. We just
need the current live stream, this
YouTube stream.
Uh, so I can stop the error.
Uh,
I'm live for 25. Okay. You know what?
Uh, you know what? You know what? You
know what?
I'm going to disable the button so I
don't get um so I don't get
uh where is it?
I'm going to disable the thing so I I
don't get interrupted.
I don't have time to fix this on stream.
Uh okay, I'll just disable the button.
Uh I have to start recording ASAP. Okay.
Uh
bro, load.
Disconnect connect.
No, don't do this to me.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Connect. Connect.
Connect. Come on. Load.
I loaded the YouTube stuff.
H. Do I have VPN?
Nope. Can it uh quit this?
Quit this. It'll quit this.
What a job fair.
Crazy. Okay, I'm going to block uh this
button.
I'm going to block
this button.
This button.
This
this this.
Yeah. Fine. You as well. Okay.
Uh okay. Everything is blocked, right?
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Have to
I'll fix it off stream. I don't I don't
have time. Uh save.
Is it okay if I uh uh normally I just
ask Chad GPT to make me a script for my
video? Uh
do you want to see me do it raw?
Okay. I have to configure my OBS.
So I'm going to not do the stream here.
So for the first time we are going to do
some OBS configuration. So we're going
to do multi- video multi- video track
stuff.
So
I'll add a canvas. So this canvas will
be
jock
avatar
only. So this is going to be an extra
canvas. Uh resolution will be
1920 by 1080. Okay.
So this is the canvas. What I'll do is
make a scene. Add
uh spout spout capture.
Oh my god, the lag is insane. Oh god.
So we will need to put you in
green screen. So color color shows.
What is this?
Nope. Uh, I need to add a color shows.
Yeah.
Color green. Yeah, that will work.
Ctrl F.
I forgot OBS stuff. I don't use obvious.
Uh, control
shift F. No, no, no. Control,
bro. The ch Oh. Oh, yeah. This is a
canvas. So, you can't use traditional
obvious stuff here. I forgot. Okay. So,
in Davinci when I edit this uh
projection uh no no way. So, lock this.
Do this. Going to put ourselves over
here. Make ourselves more bigger. That's
fine. Yeah. So, this is avatar only.
Okay. So, that's one. We add another
canvas.
We are add we have we're going to add
another canvas.
This is going to be the display.
So
oh my god.
Oh my god. Talk
display only
extra. It's a extra canvas. Yes. And
this is going to be 1920x 1080. We'll uh
do a testing and put it in uh VC and
check if it works. So technically
speaking, I I'm I will be able to right
click on VC on the recording and change
the video track. That's multitrack
video.
In this we will put
uh yeah like a display capture
normal display capture. Yeah,
that's about it. Nothing else. There's
no audio needed. That's it. And uh this
is the V. No, we don't need that.
Uh
I think I wait.
Yeah, those two is enough, right? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. So, now comes the main
thing. Settings,
output, add an output, record,
uh, record output,
multi-
video track,
recording path. I think I can put it on
C drive. Uh
uh
hybrid yeah hybrid
create recording output here I'm going
to
click on the plus
ah Sammy bruh
let's go to event manage okay I I need
to block that button.
Discord event manage. Oh, I forgot to
block you.
Block block.
All right. So, uh we don't need the main
canvas. We need avatar canvas and
display canvas. Custom encoder settings.
We're going to put a custom phone for
all of both of them.
Audio tracks. Oh, I have to set up audio
tracks. O. Uh,
we're going to do H264
and
10,000 is fine.
Yeah, there's two single pass my PC. I'm
streaming now. So,
that can be that's enough.
This one H264
single pause
audio
we can in uh I think yeah 128 is good
enough
I feel like okay
so uh what I would need will be mic and
game capture
right okay that would mean I have to set
up my audio mixer stuff Uh OBS changed
this so it's a bit annoying.
So
to his mic,
right? Uh I think so.
Yeah, I think. Yeah.
Right. What? Okay. Okay. Uh where's the
record button? Wait, where is the record
button? Okay. Multitrack video. Okay.
Three, two, one.
Hello. This is a test for a multitrack
video.
Okay, that's done. Now we check the
recording.
Now we check. Oh, I was supposed to put
it here. [laughter]
It's here, by the way. No, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. Uh, I have to get VC.
Oh, frick. My VLC is broken. No,
I have to uh I have to install a VLC. Oh
lord. Uh, wing get search VLC.
Oh my god. I have to update. We'll see.
Uh
video online. Okay. We get upgrade.
We'll see.
Okay. Till it finishes install
downloading and installation.
Uh we'll check this video uh by using
open web.
Wait, can I do this? Ah, it won't work.
Uh.
Uh. How do I Oh, it's going to install.
Okay.
You're [clears throat] working on
something. I'm sorry I read your message
late. Yeah, we're going to record a
video for I'm going to do that. I'm a
bit late.
Uh VLC.
Okay, it's working. Okay. Right click,
open with
VC media player.
So I right click here. Video.
>> Hello. This is
>> video track.
>> See, see. Oh my god. Wait. Did you see
it? Wait, wait, wait. It actually
worked. Look, look, look, look. Right
click,
bro. Bro, look. H stupid.
>> Okay. Video.
>> Video track.
V.
Pause.
Video.
Video track. This.
It's taking a bit while to load.
Where's the Where's the thing? Okay.
Wait.
In this. Wait. Where is it? Hello. Yeah,
yeah, yeah. See, see, see, see, see. So,
what when I edit the video, my uh avatar
is separate and the display capture will
be separate. Good.
Nice. Okay, let's start recording. Okay,
I'm going to
end it, right? I can just refresh this.
Okay, after I end the stream, I'll just
refresh the 24x7 channel stuff. Uh,
hi. Uh, what else? I can close this.
Should I make a PowerPoint presentation?
Should I quickly make a PowerPoint
presentation to explain for people who
don't get technical things
rather than over explaining? I think a
PowerPoint presentation will be better.
No,
I think I should do that. Uh I feel like
I should do a PowerPoint presentation,
man.
Should I?
Hello, Karina.
Also, I'll get my background music up.
Sorry,
I'll get my background music up.
Wait, what's the best way to make a
PowerPoint presentation? Uh, like quick
quick. Do do any any of you know
what you're doing? I'm going to record a
video for my 24x7 channel just to giving
you a explanation uh what why I made it
what what's it about and then I have to
make a technical detail video for those
who are interested about like about the
technical things how did I make it
everything
oh yeah oh yeah yeah I have to make the
top this thing right so I go on Twitch
Where is Asmin gold? Uh
yeah, I can just make I can take example
of As 24x7 channel. Uh no, he's on a
category now. So I think I have to find
Where is Peanut?
Bro, my browser is lagging now. What the
heck?
Okay, it's lagging.
Okay, it's back. Uh, peanut. Peanut.
I'll just uh search
always on. So, uh, when I start the
topic, I can just talk about
24x7 streams in general, right? How
they're made. Then I have to talk about
the paid thingy that will be
cloud OBS.
That will be
IL hosting and
where is it? Where is it? Andy's cuff.
This is $3,000, right? 200. How much is
this
for? Okay. 90 a month. And this I have
to talk about this as well.
You can do Yeah, you can do these two.
And another one. 24x7
OBS stream cloud.
Where is it? Uh
yeah, AutoPo. Yeah, this guy. And
then another
website I saw was
uh
uh Lenode, huh?
Okay, I think I can maybe talk about
this uh how to run it on a private
server or maybe using this.
Do I need a talk in detail?
Rick,
I don't know.
Hello, Kelly.
Welcome
PC cook to y.
Okay, so
uh
topics topics topics topics. Uh
wait, people will see my thoughts bar.
Do I need to worry about that? Let me
close this.
Why is my message getting sucked to by
mod? Wait, what? Where? Where?
Do
where? How? What?
Oh, [laughter] autumn word. Hello.
Sorry.
Uh, I missed you too.
Was there any message? Hello, Crystal
Ball 20. Wait, when did you message? Oh
my god. Why am I not seeing kick chat?
What the heck?
Ah, I'll fix that. Okay. Did someone
chat on beam? Oh, I can't see it.
Um,
also Charity, I need you.
I need you right now.
I need I need to
I need to do the script, bro. Uh,
why does this channel exist? What does
it mean for Jolex? What do I What should
I expect when I Okay, that one.
Uh,
okay. So, I think I can uh
do a normal recording. Uh that's Do you
want to do it together? Uh like a uh
Oh, I didn't check the audio now. Uh one
second.
Does this have an Oh,
I closed it.
[gasps] I closed it.
M
do you hear anything from this?
God, I can't hear anything.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
uh
canvas.
Oh, I have to manually add the Oh my
god. Wait, that's a thing.
Okay, wait. Uh oh. How do I see my
canvas? [laughter]
Tools help.
Bro, how do I see my canvas?
Plug in.
No.
Oh, this I'm using uh this one. I'm
using atom
stream suit. This one
I'm using atom stream suit.
Streamsuit. This one I'm using this.
That's why uh it feels a bit different
than usual.
Wait, how do I view my canvas? Uh,
fire. No dark. Help.
Multi dark. No, no, no tools. No
help. No.
What the heck? Where is the canvas? I
can't find the canvas. Where? Why?
Canvas. Okay, this one
management canvas. Okay, wait. But the
question I have is
how in the world can I access my Oh,
it's over here. Okay. Okay. This is my
avatar now. So, what I have to do here
is add my mic, right? My ox.
And this mic ox is running my Elgato
thingy, right? This one with noise
suppression and a compressor. Yeah.
Uh okay. Uh
that is good. Uh but wait a [music]
minute.
Wait, how do I um
check check?
Uh confusing.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Or [clears throat] do you want me to do
it here? I don't know.
We'll do a test run. Okay. I'm going to
do a test run. Okay.
All right. We're going to [music] do a
test run. Uh, also I'm just going to add
one more recording track
output. Uh,
recording path
here. hybrid.
Uh, so
this is only for the avatar. Okay.
Custom encoder
H.264.
Let let that be default single pass.
Audio should be mic.
Okay.
All right.
This is a test to check if I'm audible
on the avatar only version recording.
Okay, it's done.
Check the video.
This is a test to check if I'm audable
on the avatar only version recording.
Okay, it works. Okay, okay, okay.
Wait, no, wait. Okay, okay, it works.
Uh, that works. [music] Then I have to
do a another recording test for the
display capture, right? For the
multitrack.
uh
jock display only.
I'll arrange all of this later. I'm just
going to wing it.
Single pass. Oh, wait. No.
Custom encoder
dock display.
This will be this
single pass. Audio will be mic.
Hi. Okay.
This is a test to check if I am audable
when I'm doing the screen capture
recording for the multitrack.
Okay.
Check the video.
This is a test to check if I'm audible.
I'm doing track.
But do you think I need it? Like when I
do the test, [music] it'll sound like
this.
Uh checking testing avatar plus display
multitrack recording.
So when I do the test
open with real.
Oh, wait. You guys can hear it. I can't
hear it cuz uh it's feeding through the
feeding through the
Yeah. Yeah, it's audable. So, avatar
testing works.
I'm impatar
works. Uh,
oh my god. Video track.
Yeah, recording and aviator both are
working. Yeah, good.
I'm 100% sure uh if this does not work,
I'm going to just uh redo the whole
thing off stream, man.
Okay,
close this. Hi, enjoy the background
music. Hi, let's start.
Do I have my script ready? [laughter] I
don't have a script, bro.
Also, storage check. How much storage do
I have?
Holy lord, we are struggling on storage.
[laughter]
It's okay. It's okay. It won't be too
much. Uh,
it won't be too much. It won't be too
much. Um.
Uh.
Okay. Uh, it's going to be a five minute
video, right? Okay. Hi. Okay. I'm going
to do it. Okay, [laughter]
wish me luck. You're going to see a live
raw dogging
of me recording. Uhhuh.
Oh god, help me.
One second. Um
Um
put this here
actually. Okay, it's okay. It's okay.
>> [clears throat]
>> Wait, how do I view my uh view my
canvases
talks?
Isn't the latest obvious? Uh you can
like dock your
Yeah. Okay. this.
Hi.
Oh my god. Let's go. [laughter]
Hi. Uh, am I okay? Okay. Hi.
Uh,
all right. Okay.
Three,
two,
help me. Three, two, one,
go.
Hello everyone and welcome to a new
video. So this video we'll be talking
about
my always on 24x7
jockn channel. Hi. So if you have
noticed recently I had made an
announcements on my community tab on
YouTube and my other socials that I have
launched like a 24x7 always on channel
which is currently even now live
streaming on Twitch, YouTube and kick.
So it's it's a channel dedicated to
uh like a [music] series of memories of
past broadcast I have done on my journey
as a YouTuber. So it's basically all the
YouTube uh streams I have done. Yeah. So
in this video I just wanted to clarify
why did I decide to launch uh always on
channel like that and what's the purpose
of it and why now
is that good.
[clears throat]
Should I read them?
Uh I got edit and post there. So yeah.
Um
the reason why I decided to make a
separate 24x7 channel for myself [music]
is because
I for those who don't know I will be
leaving
uh for those who don't know I will be
leaving to Japan by April of 2026. fix.
So that means it keeps open a
unpredictable
door for me like I wouldn't know when
I'm able to live stream
[\h__\h] read
the reason why I decided to do a 25x7
channel is due to for those who don't
know I will be leaving to Japan on to
April 2 26th
So that keeps the door open of
unpredictability where I myself isn't
sure when I will be able to return back
to streaming
and in a way my content
is basically live streaming and I do
videos here and there but for those who
love to watch me live and stuff I wanted
to keep uh some sort sort of memories
some way or sort so that people can
remember me. So that's why I decided to
make the 24x7 channel so that all my
concert plates and conell
all my concert plates and constellers
can enjoy old and new
content [music] whenever I'm not
actively present.
God cut.
Hello Parasite Gaming. Welcome, welcome.
We are recording a YouTube video.
Welcome, man. Currently recording.
Um,
I thought I reach.
How many minutes has it been? I can't
say the timer, bro.
Okay. Uh,
I have to write it down. What? I forget.
What did I What am I supposed to say?
Yo,
why?
What's
purpose?
Uh,
what's the purpose? And I'm struggling,
man. This is bad. I don't think I can do
this live.
I don't think I can do this live
purpose. Uh Taj help me. Uh
holding it
points. Oh, I need I need pointers. I
need pointers,
bro. I need pointers. Uh
One second.
Uh, open hook.
You know what? I'm going to re redo the
take. Okay. One second.
What this channel is? Okay.
Why I made it.
Yeah. And what it's not about. Yeah.
That's I have to write that.
[cough]
What the viewers should expect? Why it's
still matters to you.
and the closing.
So, it's basically going to be a five
minute video. That's it. Don't run.
Don't mess in. Okay. Uh, don't explain,
Sammy. Okay. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi.
You know what? I'm just going to keep
this here. You know what? I need this.
Hi.
[laughter]
break.
Okay.
So,
oh, one second. Uh, I need to keep this
over here.
I need my Twitch chat over there.
Hi
>> [clears throat]
[cough]
>> Okay. [music] Three, two, one.
Hello everyone.
So, this video is going to be about the
24x7 channel. I will be listing out
Wait, redo.
How do I do the intro, bro?
How do I do the intro?
Hello everyone. This is Joex.
Before the start of this video, I would
like to uh
we do before the start of this video, I
would like to give an explanation on
a few things. Why this channel exists?
What is this channel about? Why I made
it? And what's it not about? And what
you should expect from this channel,
[music]
and why is why it matters to me. Wait,
is that good?
I suck being a creator, bro. [laughter]
N I need inspiration. M
I need inspiration.
Damn. He made a new update to the to his
what?
Okay. It's I I It's like, how should I
phrase it? It's like I'm making like a
upd, right?
Okay,
fine. I'll
redo
one second.
This is not working, man.
This is not working at all.
Okay. [clears throat]
How do YouTubers make their stuff?
Okay. Hi. Hi. Hi. [clears throat]
Bring water. I need water.
>> [clears throat]
>> 3 2 1
Hello everyone. This is Jocnex.
We are going 24 hours.
So [music] for those who don't know
recently I have launched a 24 hours
channel which is broadcasting all of my
YouTube streams
which I have done on my YouTube channel.
So
this video is uh giving you a brief some
u so this video is going to be about
this video is going to give you a brief
information about what the 24 hours
channel is about.
Firstly,
I made the 24-hour channel because I
wanted everyone
to have
something of me when I'm not there, when
I'm not able to stream like or go live
due to due to life or anything. I wanted
my community to be able to watch and
enjoy the older condensants we have
experienced and made memories in the
past. I wanted you guys to enjoy it
again.
It's like
rewatching memories we have shared
before. Yeah. So that's why the 24 hours
channel excess. That's why I made it
and this channel is going to be live
always 24x7
and
but
it won't mean that I'm actually live on
my main channel.
Please remember that there may be
instances where the 24
where the 24-hour channel would be live
and I will also be live but in the
future I'll make it so that whenever I'm
live on my main channels the 24 hours
stream will get paused but it still be
live.
So whenever you see the 24-hour channel
live that means it's replaying all the
past memories we had of jognex
and why I made it is because I noticed
that a lot of people in my community
have missed certain streams they
couldn't watch some stuff and everyone
has different time zones and also So
this year, April 2026, I'm moving to
Japan. So it's an unpredictable
situation where I myself don't know if
I'm able if I'll be able to stream or
provide live streams for you guys. So I
wanted something to be out there so that
you guys can remember me by that I exist
and we share all these memories.
And I would like to take a moment to
clarify some assumptions on what this
24hour channel is not about. [music]
Firstly,
this channel is not meant for farming
engagements or
anything like that. It won't be a
replacement for my main live streams
ever. And it's not pretending to be a
live stream. It's basically
a rerun.
It's rebroadcasting my previous content
I have streamed before. So technically
it is live but it's not live life live.
So please do remember that whenever you
come across my 24x7 channel
uh streams on YouTube kick or Twitch
[music] remember the chats won't be
moderator for now.
And if you do send a message over there
in the chat rooms, uh I won't be able to
see it.
And also you won't be talking to me
directly how my usual streams are where
you can chat in the live chat and I'll
read it and interact with you. So yeah,
please do remember that
this channel exists even if there's no
one barely watching is because as I
mentioned before, I wanted to give
something of me to be existent out there
when I'm not there there.
And what
my community and my viewers can should
expect from this 24-hour channel is
you might see the same content again. It
will be basically all the older WS of
all the playlists in my YouTube channel.
Those will be recycled and rebroadcasted
here and there. [music] So you'll see
some random moments from random streams
from like 2021 to or maybe the current
uh 2026 streams like that. It'll be
randomized or sequential and sometimes
yeah the chat will be empty in these 24x
channels. It's okay as long as you guys
can take a moment of your time to
remember me by or enjoy these moments
together
as a group with everyone together. It
means a lot to me.
And one of the main thing I would like
to say that is
even if no one is watching my 24-hour
channels, I like knowing that it exists.
Maybe someday someone will some maybe
someday someone will stumble into this
and see these moments and they'll
[music]
be interested to check my main channel
or my condent out, right? So, it will be
a good opener for people who are
discovering me or [music] interested to
check me out or those who watch me, they
can still feel the nostalgia and such.
And finally I um wanted to say that
anyone you guys are welcome to stick
around and lurk in these 24x
in these 24x7 channel and
yeah and do not worry my main channel
content everything will be the same.
This is a separate
this is a separate 24x7 and stuff. So
yeah, if you like to know more updates
and technical details and stuff, I will
be making a different video regarding
it. And if my 24hour setup uh has any
updates and announcements, I will be
making it through my main channel like
this a video to giving you guys like an
update on what's changed and what you
can expect in the future. will have a
lot of um viewer interactive elements to
these 24x7 channels. So yeah, hope you
look forward for it and thank you for
watching. Take care everyone.
it. But okay, how many minutes is that?
[laughter]
8 minutes. Hello, the wild. We're
recording a YouTube video for for the
for the 24x7 thingy. Welcome. Hello.
Hy. Yep, yep, yep, yep. I need a
hydrate.
One second. Let me watch this. I think I
can cut some portions.
For those who don't know, recently I
have launched a 24 hours channel which
is broadcasting all of my YouTube
streams.
>> Am I legally blind already?
>> Which I have done on my YouTube channel.
>> What? I don't hear anything.
This video is uh giving you a brief some
um so this video
Okay, we can edit this real quick. Uh,
okay.
It's uh I I took so many takes and I
kind of winged [music] it again. Uh,
it's supposed to be like a five minute
thingy or something. Uh, yeah. So, I'm
planning to make two videos. One is like
a short brief introduction like what
uh
uh like what uh like short brief
introduction like what the main uh
24hour channel is about. And
the second video uh second video I'm
going to make is the technical details
is literally going to be savvy stuff.
[gasps]
Oh my god.
Uh yeah, I'll check after stream kind of
key.
Are you a bit sick? Yeah, I had my
vacation. My um my Yeah, I'm a bit sick
cuz of traveling and stuff.
I need to hydrate, man.
Yeah. So, technical details. Now, uh I
have to explain about these three. Where
was your vacation? Uh I went uh with
family.
Uh we visited like churches and some
hilly areas and everything. It was like
around southern side of India. Yeah.
Different state.
Oh boy.
Oh. Okay. Got it. Got it. Got it.
Gotcha.
But the thing is now I don't want to I
can't even talk about YouTube DLPs.
Should I make a PowerPoint presentation?
A part of me is like telling like doc
you should make a PowerPoint
presentation.
people won't get what the heck you are
even saying right
I'm worried what should I do
my old setup
wow
okay let me open doc let me finish
editing I think uh the
I'll just finish the 8 minute video real
quick, speedrun it and uh then I'll do
the technical video. Okay, then we'll uh
wrap up and I'll share with the real
[clears throat]
new India version of the virus that
caused by No, no, no, not that. No, no.
It's just a normal cough from cold.
There's an Indian version of a virus.
Wow. I didn't even know.
That crazy.
Damn.
That's crazy.
Wow.
I I followed the Nati's tutorial thingy.
Nati's tutorial thing.
Uh Nati's uh the new video Nati made,
right? Like the multitrack audio stuff.
[clears throat]
I I I just finished [music] setting that
up.
Wait, how do you blur?
Uh,
jog 247
intro video.
going for a new in country.
I don't even I never heard about it too.
Uh okay. Uh wait, I have to be careful.
Yep. Yep. Yep.
How do you edit? the
project settings
timeline.
Wait, how do you edit the timeline?
Play back
quarter.
Okay, I don't think you can hear these,
right? Uh, should I give you audio?
Okay, let me just make the audio thing
when you stream with multiple different
like OBS mel this and that it's so
confusing sometimes.
Dainci dari
monitoring it. Oh,
crazy
resolve.
So the
hello everyone.
Why does the quality Okay. Okay. I
forgot. Uh how do I add effects? Uh
[cough]
no, wait. Uh I have to search for chroma
key.
No green. Uh
wait, what's it called? Oh my god, I
forgot, bro. Uh
what is it called?
It is loud. Okay, thank you. thing. Uh
broadcasting all of my YouTube streams
which I have done on my YouTube channel.
My YouTube. Okay. Thank you. [music]
Thank you. Thank you for letting me
know. Thank you.
Effect uh
filter box. No
way.
Oh,
what?
[cough]
Wait, am I not supposed to do it from
fusion? I forgot how to do this.
Oh my god, I forgot how to do this mask.
Yeah.
channel.
Uh
key chrome. Oh, yeah.
Create a mat from a blue or green
screen.
Uniform color background. Wait, isn't it
dela key here?
Matt.
Oh, key background color.
This
There you go.
Does it look a bit greeny?
No.
Oh, that's it. Easy. [laughter] Okay.
Okay. Black video. Um,
okay. Let's edit that.
No, wait. I'll use the AI tools for this
AI tool.
Uh,
[clears throat]
wait. Firstly, save it.
Get rid of that effects.
Ah, I forgot. Uh well uh wait wait wait.
Um I think I have to do firstly I have
to do
AI tools
create subtitles from audio.
What is this
[clears throat]
summer?
[laughter]
[snorts]
I don't I still don't get it.
Why do people make that do that though
thingy?
That's crazy.
That's crazy. Crazy.
I I still don't get it. But damn.
So, my inspiration for this is not I'm
going to do it like he did. Coage
did.
Um
yeah, I'm going to do it like this. I
think he has a video about it. Red is
busy is lagging.
Okay, at the back I think.
Where is the video?
Yeah, in a way my ultimate goal is not
for my 24hour thingy is I want to make
it like this like co how code did it
like a 24 like a viewer v watered rerun
system.
Yeah, it's so crazy. No. Hello be
welcome.
Yeah, I want people to vote what kind of
uh what kind of board they want to
watch. That's the main idea.
I still don't know. I I feel like like
see see when you look at co uh 24 hours
down no what you see here is this is a
YouTube embed
but which has a custom JavaScript
running behind cuz it gives you the
title of the currently playing VOD
that uh close caption is is on.
Then here this is something cool like it
also gives you the time code
that is crazy and nice
and I don't get this block system he has
it will be in the ver this thing.
Yeah. Oh yeah. This is the video. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. So I'm I thought so his
video
>> go here. Yeah, he made it in 3 minutes.
Meanwhile, I'm too I think I may mine is
8 minute now. I have to make it shorter.
Yeah, I just wanted to give like a short
introduction what what is it about and
everything like that.
Yeah, my PC will go
but this is cool. Ah viewers can log in
via Twitch and they can vote
they can vote which content they want to
see. So for example he provides like all
the playlist for the content right
they can play see 88 people voted for
blueprint stream playlist and if you
click on it it shows the
playlist of all the that is nice
I don't know how he did this I I I think
for me Since I don't know coding now,
it's going to be hard. But this is like
internally coded.
It fetches all the streams
from YouTube, right?
Like if I edit the URL and make it like
YouTube.com.
Oh, wait. Never mind. Wait, wait.
Is it different?
Is it different? [music]
I think it's a bit different. Wait, hold
up.
I think it's a bit different. Go Carage.
Oh. Oh, wait. He adds thumbnail to
everything. Oh,
blueprints.
Oh. Oh, okay. It is from the playlist.
Okay.
Okay. It is from okay. Okay. Oh, it is
from the playlist. Ah,
okay.
Wait, why is it only 30 minutes? Oh,
[music] yeah. He plays other streams.
So, me? Uh, yeah, I'm a little sick
today. Don't worry. I'll heal up soon, I
think.
Wait, is someone from is like 30
minutes, 40 minutes? Damn.
Wait, I I feel like
Oh, wait, wait, wait. It's like he
doesn't show the whole stream. Only
only shows the game play of that segment
of that specific stream. Oh, that's
smart.
Oh, that's smart. Oh my god, that's so
Ah, that is so smart.
So, it's not a live stream, it's a
video. Ah, that is so smart.
Oh,
if I was streaming on Twitch, if Twitch
was my main thing,
um, I could have done that.
Uh
but yeah, for me, my case, it's like
mine will be a full stream. So the
people who will be watching a specific
war, they had to sit through the whole
thing. I guess you can't skip it.
I don't know. Maybe in the future we'll
have stuff. Okay, let me finish editing.
So, here's where we start, right? Do I
need subtitles? I don't think we need uh
you're going to program or code, then it
will be a fun adventure for sure. Yeah,
if I knew coding. No, that would have
been so great. I could have done so much
things.
Play back.
How do I view the transcript?
God, I don't know how to use this.
Why did I make a subtitle?
I don't need this.
New game play. [laughter] It's a gorilla
stream. There you go.
Everyone, this is
going
>> Jocnox. Oh my god,
I want to cry.
Wait, how do I view transcripts?
Ah, this button.
Oh,
we are going 24 hoursish.
Uh,
[clears throat] what's a gorilla stream?
Okay. Gorilla stream means
um it's an unplanned unscheduled stream.
Normally a YouTuber stream is always
going to be scheduled content. uh
YouTubers going to like
I JP YouTubers they will schedule what
type of stream they are going to do a
week ahead or like they'll have their
schedule no like Monday Tuesday
Wednesday Friday rest day like that uh
so gorilla stream means uh it's an
unplanned stream I am out of nowhere
streaming if you look it Stop g uh
gurelia
stream.
Uh stop gurelia stream. Yeah, gorilla
stream is an unscheduled surprise live
broadcast by connect creators part
particular popular among YouTubers that
happens without prior announcement or
outside of a regular schedule.
These ambush streams are designed to
surprise viewers often announced last
minute on social media or stating
abruptly. Yeah.
Hello Salah. Welcome.
Yeah. A random stream. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
That's a gorilla stream. Not gorilla.
Hello. [snorts]
[clears throat]
Okay. Uh we're going for those who don't
know recently I've launched it at a time
which is working all of my YouTube
streams which I've done on my YouTube
channel. So this video is going to give
you a brief
I have to make a edit over here.
I don't want to see the SRT
thingy. Can I delete this?
Hello Ryland. Welcome,
welcome, welcome. My day was good. I
just came back from vacation.
Joke next. Blame the
AI or the audio subtitle for recognizing
my voice.
assuming I said jock next. When I said
jock next.
[laughter]
[gasps]
>> Hello.
This is Jock.
>> Okay, that's a Okay, wait. I think I can
do the ripple delete. I [music] think
timeline
audio.
Uh video. Uh no AI.
How do I ripple delete? Uh
wait.
I join audio.
Ah ripple delete silence. Okay. May I
copy this?
Ripple delete silence.
I can adjust this.
[laughter]
Man,
I'm not the snack.
[laughter]
Okay. Uh, I think I got just a little
bit.
[clears throat]
Pretty good so far. Okay. remove.
And we got our edited thingy and I can
just adjust. Hi, [music] Alex. Watch.
>> See, jock next. I say it rightly.
>> Wait,
>> does it sound like Doc Knack? Wait,
is this Capka? No, Davinci.
We are going 24 hours.
Recently I have launched 24 hours
channel which is
all of my YouTube streams which I have
done on my YouTube channel.
>> So this video is about giving you
some video.
>> Okay. Okay. Cut cut cut. Okay. I need a
cut this out
a X
and do that.
>> I can I think I can just cut this part
as well and move this out.
Twinsies.
>> So, this video is going to be about
[laughter] this video is going to be
information about what
channel is about. Firstly,
okay, I think I can remove this guy.
Also, a lot of space.
Yeah, a lot of space.
Oh boy. Okay.
24 channel because I wanted everyone
to have something of me when I'm not
there when I'm not able to stream live
or anything.
I wanted my community to be able to
watch and enjoy the old
experience and memories in the past. I
want uh how's the screen movie? Uh
[music] it's a setting in uh Mel Studio.
Not obvious. Uh you go
uh you unlock the secret mode over here.
Then you can just uh click on it display
capture and [music]
you click on the option capture cursor.
You can adjust the zoom cer zoom. So
wherever you move my stream is lagging
cuz so many stuff happening. But yeah,
where wherever you move it can move. Oh
my god, my stream is lagging, bro. What
the heck?
Is it because of you?
I'm not doing my 24 V channel right.
What is the V 24 jocknik doing? Ah the
jockathon feedback form the Google form.
Okay. Anyway,
uh yeah, that's how I do in OBS. If you
wish to do that, there's a plugin called
>> [clears throat]
>> uh
mouse
call
zoom obvious. I think uh this one
obvious lua mouse uh zoom to mouse. You
install this and this how you do it. And
if you go if you check the GitHub of
this person, you'll also see me cuz I
suggested a version. I think uh
where's the GitHub?
I think I suggested like a older
version.
Um I think they credited me. I think not
sure
what the Oh, wait. That was not this
plugin. It's a different plugin.
Yeah, I suggested the remote version.
Yeah, remote. So, if you have a two or
three or four uh two two three p uh PC
setup, if you want to control the mouse
thingy,
it'll uh like remotely for a different
source, it'll be you use the remote
stuff.
Yeah.
Hello, parasite.
Motion sickness. No. Yeah, let me just
undo this so we can just see the whole
thing as it is.
Hello, Parasite Gaming. Welcome
in the past. I wanted you guys to enjoy
it again. It's like
>> enjoy it again. There's a gap.
Is this good enough? contents we have
[music] experienced and made memories in
the past. I wanted you guys to enjoy it
again. It's like rewatching memories we
have shared. Do you remember a guy who
said who he wanted to be a YouTuber? Oh,
was it you? I I think I remember it. Is
Is it Isn't it from the stream I was
playing Arc Raiders?
Yeah. Yeah.
Uh, okay. Then what else? Uh,
do I need a cut over here?
>> Excit
is also interested in trying out
YouTubing, right?
>> So that's why the 24 hours
exists. That's why I made it. And this
channel is going to be live
24x7.
>> Yeah, I remember. I remember. I
remember. Yes.
How is it going? Did you Did you do you
like video? How was it so far when you
tried it out?
[clears throat]
always
but it won't
actually live on my main channel. Please
remember that there may be instances
where the 24
channel
I think I can cut it here.
Oh, nice.
>> Where?
Ah, the bear. I can cut the bear.
Ah, do I I think I mumble sometimes. No
pain. Okay, I will cut this part. Fine.
Wait, what content did you do? Parish
[clears throat]
60 subs. Let's go.
Now you got to put like smaller smaller
milestones like 100 then to 500 then
to,000 slowly slowly.
24 channel
would be live and I will also be live
but in the future I'll make it so that
whenever I'm
that [snorts]
why do I have to manually cut the
silences? I thought the AI silence
remover did it. Wow.
The 24 hours stream will get paused but
soon be live. So whenever you see the Ah
just me that when I hear my voice I die
hearing out of Yeah, me too. Me too. I
got used to this. It It took a while.
It's I still don't I still hate my
voice. But uh
[clears throat]
uh I'm you got you have to the thing now
when you're starting to become when
you're a content creator when you do
everything by yourself. You got to get
used to uh watching your own streams.
sit down and watch your own streams and
go through it
like to make clips and stuff yourself.
No. So in a way over time we'll get used
to it. I think whenever I'm live on my
main channels the 24 stream will get
paused but it still be live. So whenever
you see the 24th channel live that means
it's replaying all the Last memories we
had all the darkness
we had of chaot
in a way I feel like I could do a
retake. I don't know.
>> When I was trying to sing I did Oh yeah,
I did that. I I can't listen to myself
sing. It's so bad. I want to break
something. It's like
I don't know
the feeling of
hi uh digging a hole and hiding in a
hole. That's what I feel.
missed certain streams. They couldn't
watch some stuff.
>> Okay, this line which I took it from
Chad Japet
uh that doesn't matter much because
people
uh who can't watch my streams, who watch
uh uh who can't watch my streams or
catch me live due to time zone and
stuff, they can see the video content.
Why? [music]
But in in a way it contradicts the
video. Uh I don't know.
Basically, it's a love rerun channel.
So, I don't know if I should put this
part. I don't know. But it's fine
because I noticed that a lot of people
in my community have missed certain
streams. They couldn't watch some stuff
and everyone has different Amazon and
also this year April 2026 I'm moving to
Japan. So it's an entrepreneur.
>> Okay. This will be my main reason for
making the war channel like not war the
24x7 channel.
Let's hope my family um won't do
something uh dumb with my PC at home.
This PC, the one you're looking at.
[laughter] Well, let's hope it last for
an year.
Okay. Without me maintaining it and no,
I can maintain it remotely.
Yeah. But but still internal issues. No,
like uh like I have to like what if the
BIOS doesn't boot all those issues. Now,
let's hope that doesn't happen or I'm
doomed, bro. Or I have to pay like how
much? Did I close that? Or I have to pay
$90 per month for having a cloud OBS
server, which I don't want to do. I
would love to do, but nah. No, I'm
broke.
Uh, I think I can do 60. No, no, wait. I
need the
Sammy and everything, right? So, I have
to do 90.
So expensive.
>> Situation where I myself don't know if
I'm able If I'll be able to
able don't know if I'm able if I'll be
able don't know if okay if I am
what is the reason to go to Japan.
Good question. Uh
I [clears throat] don't know. Uh it's
just to chase my dreams.
uh
and [music]
it comes with a lot of uncertainty. It's
like it's like think about this uh yeah
you have seen people who move to a new
city, new country to start a new life,
right? They don't know what they are
going into. They want to start a new and
be independent [music] try to do
everything there themselves and go uh
like face all the issues everything and
overcome the challenges and actually get
somewhere they are where they are stable
and have a good job and get they can be
settled and stuff kind of like that.
[clears throat]
Uh you can say like that I think but I
never I the reason for me to go to Japan
is actually because I love YouTubing.
Vubing originated from like Japan right
like idle culture and stuff. Plus I love
music too Japanese music. So I have a
lot of backup plans either get into a
industry or uh a job or something which
uh like does
um
like does like YouTubing management or
something where I help YouTubers or
maybe uh become a talent myself or
something or if the path of YouTubing or
entertainment industry is hard then I
can do music industry
uh or underground on under underground
[music]
music artist kind of thingy DJ shows and
all those stuff I could do I think
[music]
then you will be asking who's going to
watch an random Indian in Japan uh make
music and uh DJ and stuff that's a good
question but yeah I don't know I I'm
just going to wing it if that doesn't
work I have other backup plans too
Yeah,
in a way. Yeah, but the thing is uh I
don't want to depend or rely too much on
my family money. Once I got a part times
and everything once I'm there for the
first year of after the first year
everything is going to be dependent by
me myself
finances everything I don't
[clears throat] want to rely on a third
party at all.
I'm already a spoiled brat
as a only child. So yeah, don't know if
I'm able if I'll be able
if I'm if I'm able if I'll be able
I got thing again. [music]
But from here
to here,
whatever you're saying is my goal, too.
I want to be acting and make my money a
pro. That's it. Yeah. Let's do our best.
Okay.
I really hope things work out, you know.
Uh there will be people who um I mean
there will be people who will be
worrying. They'll give you their side of
things but again it is your life it is
your
stuff right you got to face it others
are there as
mediums or people will be there or paris
everyone like they can only guide you or
give you choices
in the end you you are the one who's
going to take the choice make the final
decision
Walk the path, right?
Yeah.
So, yeah.
[cough]
A fade makes us me teacher likes to do
our best. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I
would love to meet
provide live streams for you.
>> Oh,
delete
>> something to be out there so that you
guys can remember
that I exist and we share all these
memories. And I would like to take a
moment to clarify some assumptions on
what this 24hour channel is not about.
Okay, this is the important part.
uh
you know there were so many people I
mean I saw comments I guess uh who were
like
[cough] excuse me I made it so much
obvious that it's a rerun it's not live
it's a rerun channel but still so many
people are so confused
why is the streamer not talking
um this and that, this and that. Is this
a broadcast? Is this the fake stream?
This and that.
It literally says in the title, it says
in the comments.
I don't know what I have to do more than
you. I did my best, but some people are
not understanding. And there were like
other criticisms to like why a smaller
creator
who barely gets uh viewers um need to do
a 24x7 channel save your CPU uh your PC
power ality build this and that cuz the
current system is local now it's not
cloud based right all of that stuff but
I I I think I forgot to mention in the
video, but uh it's an experimental
it's an experimental thing I wanted
[music] to do. If it works, it works. If
it doesn't work, it's fine.
Show you. I don't think I'll keep it
forever. Maybe if there's demand or if
or if I can afford it. So, yeah, I just
had dinner now. Nice. I I already had my
dinner like at 8 p.m.
[cough]
But it's like you try it's like trial
and error.
I just want to try out stuff which no
one has tried it before and see how it
goes. It's a good learning material for
others as well
cuz I'm taking the risk right trial and
error.
And [clears throat] you can see if did
it work out for me? Maybe not. If it
doesn't, how can you make it better?
That's content creation, right?
assions on what this hour channel is
[clears throat] not about. Firstly, this
channel is not meant for farming
engagements or anything like that. It
won't be a replacement for my main live
streams ever. And it's not pretending to
be a live stream. It's basically
a rerun. It's rebroadcasting my previous
content I have streamed with
at the gap need
close the gap. Okay,
>> so technically it is live but it's not
live. So please do remember that
whenever you come across my 24x channel
streams on YouTube or Twitch remember
the chat won't be moderated for now and
if you do send a message over there in
the chat rooms I won't be
oh god in the future now
I will make it a 24x7 moderator I know
I'll I'll hire more I guess. I don't
know if there's more people watching it.
>> How my usual streams are where you can
chat in the live chat
[cough and clears throat]
with you.
that this channel exists even if there's
no one watching.
I I wanted to say this channel will
exist if there's no one barely watching
this.
>> If there's no one barely watching is
because as I mentioned before, I wanted
to give something of me to be existent
out there when I'm not
And what my community and my viewers can
expect from this 24 channel is you might
see the same content again.
>> Man, my base channel is you might see
the same content again. It will be
basically all the older VS of all the
playlist on my YouTube channel. Those
will be recycled and rebed here and
there. So you'll see some
>> What do you mean by recycle
like 2021
or maybe the current 2026?
I didn't have to make the ear
>> sometimes. Yeah, the chat will be empty,
but it's [music] okay as long as you
guys can take a moment of time to
remember or enjoy these moments together
as a group of everyone together. It
means a lot
moments together
as a group of everyone together. It
means a lot to me. I don't think I need
the last spot at this point.
Together is enough as a group.
Uh yeah, I think
it should be enough.
>> One of the main thing I would like to
say that is even if no one [cough]
I like knowing that it exists. Maybe
someday someone will
Maybe someday someone will stumble.
>> Okay, [music] I stumbled here.
>> Maybe someday someone will stumble into
this.
>> Okay, here and
see these moments and they'll be
interested to check my main channel or
my out, right? So, it will be a good
opener for people who are discovering me
or interested to check me out or those
who watch me, they can still feel the
nostalgia and such. And finally, I
wanted to say that anyone you guys are
welcome to stick around and anyone is to
recone.
Okay.
Uh you guys
and
these in these 247 channel
in these
in these two
in the Okay [clears throat]
channel.
Yeah. And do not worry my main channel
will come everything will be the same.
This is a separate this is a separate
>> what
>> this is this is
>> this is a separate okay
and stuff if you like to know more
updates and technical details and stuff
I will be making a different video
regarding it and my 24hour setup uh has
any updates [music] and announcements. I
will be making it through my main
channel like this a video to giving you
guys like an update on what's changed
and what you can expect in the future.
We'll have a lot of
interactive elements to these 24x7
channels. So yeah, hope you look forward
for it and thank you for watching. Take
care everyone.
Bye-bye.
>> Okay, it's not bad.
Uh I think I I think it's not bad.
[cough]
Um it's not bad, isn't I? I think I
don't know.
I
need a background.
But do I need a video? I don't know. I
I've been doing so much of these black
and white kind of thingy. I I don't
know, man.
Uh add a track
digital grar.
drone overlay. What is this? Okay. Uh,
[clears throat]
night vision. Damn. Okay. Uh, what am I
looking for? Color shows, generators,
contours, cosmetics, cloud,
solid color,
or color gradient.
I would love a fuller color. No, wait.
I Yeah, I would love a full color
gradient. Let's see how that goes.
[clears throat]
Make it two color.
That one.
Do I need the yellows? No, I want my
pinks.
Okay, this is good, I think. Uh, don't
know what I'm doing. Don't mind me.
Uh,
move for a cup.
How do I Okay, like this.
[clears throat]
So basically we're done.
>> We are going 24 hours. So for those who
don't know recently I have launched a 24
hours channel which is broadcasting all
of my YouTube streams which I have.
Okay. Save this. Save. Save. Save. Save.
And I'm going to render it and upload it
to YouTube. Okay. Right now, this very
second. H. Okay. 1080p file. Uh,
darkness 247 intro location
can be here. Fine. Uh,
normalize audio. Yes. Optimize to
standard.
Uh
upload directly. Yes. Uh
Darkness 247 intro
and animation. No entertainment
actually.
Shave. Shave. Shave. Shave. Okay. And
add to render Q and render. Hi. We're
done with the
Should I do the second video right now?
We have been live for 20. Are we alive
for 3 hours though? Do I need to do the
technical details version? Uh
I'm so underprepared for the technical
version.
I think for the technical version, no
specifically speaking. I feel like Oh
[\h__\h] Oh my god. Stop. I just noticed
something.
Uh I forgot to fix this.
Clear render start. Okay. Render again.
Replace. Okay. Hi. Hi. Hi.
For the technical details video which is
going to be at least an 30 minute video
long. I guess
if I don't make a PowerPoint
presentation,
uh
I don't know
how I could do it.
The thing is now
I don't expect people to watch it,
but
for those who care about it, I want them
to know what they came there or came
here for. Like how can I do a 24x7
channel as a streamer who has so many
streams on my channel on their channel?
Can I do a
do for X and thingy or use it as a BRB
thingy? What can I do to those for those
questions? I want like a video out
there.
Yeah, that's the thing.
Oh, the
Sammy version.
I was trying to chat on Twitch and this
is the reason why I hate Swash. Oh,
wait. What happened? What happened? What
happened? Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What happened?
Ah, wait. Uh, for Yeah, you just made
your new account now. Oh, yeah. Yeah,
you have to verify your email
and then I don't know if I put like a
No, no, wait. You already have a Twitch
account.
Wait, what happened?
Wait, what? What happened? Where the is
it my auto mode? Is it some setting I
have?
Wait, what happened?
N
I am what I have one for ah yeah
one number that's an issue
oh wait do this um actually
you can go to your Twitch settings
and allow additional account creation
I think you can do that like go to
security
and take this option enable additional
account creation. Additional touch
accounts can be created using this
verified phone number. So
yeah you can do this either you can do
the verified phone number or verify
email address.
So you can make multiple accounts with
one either one of them.
Yeah,
that's a setting. You can do that.
Still not verifying. W That's so weird.
That sh [music]
video is done. So,
it's it's supposed to be uploaded to
it should be uploaded to my
channel,
I think.
Mhm.
Content.
Yes, it is here.
Yeah, it is here.
What? Three minute. Hello. What? Excuse
me. What the What?
What?
0.
Okay, that's wrong.
Okay, I have to manually upload it. Oh
god. Baka baka baka.
I have to manually upload this. Oh lord.
Thank god I have a original save.
There you go.
[clears throat]
Why am I made to my model situation
changed?
Should I take down this video? I don't
know. I got I I will be debuting the new
model though.
the new model I bought. I I can [music]
I I need some
I need a talk with the artist
uh for the permission and I'm ready to
uh reveal it.
No luck in Twitch. It's okay.
Okay. I should have
no luck in YouTube either. It always
lags. Stream lags.
Why is my stream lagging?
6 minute video. Okay.
Uh
okay.
unlisted.
Okay. Uh the introduction video is done.
Okay.
And um
introduction video is done. Now the
technical details version.
[clears throat] I am so unprepared.
Okay. Should I do this? Okay. Alex do
this.
How do I stream just my Oh, gotcha.
I really wish I could
add that plugin and all so It follows
the cursor kind of thing.
Why are you glitching like this? Oh my
god.
What is going on over here? Oh my god.
Okay.
[laughter] Oh my god.
Holy Lord.
>> [cough]
>> Hi. Okay.
Honestly speaking, I want to record I
would love to record this
on Melt rather than OBS,
but Mel is laggy for me right now since
I'm streaming.
Or another way I can do is now I can
just clip my stream
and upload it as a VOD for the technical
details. [music]
H
I could do that but I don't know.
Um, oh, if I leave her able to chat on
Twitch, hello Bing from Twitch.
Let's go.
You did it.
So many turned off stuff.
[snorts]
>> [clears throat]
>> where it would check for my current
scene.
Make a playlist.
What is this? Channel points. Channel
points uh uh you can earn it when you
watch and engage with the stream live
stream. [music] They can redeem stuff
over the Twitch live stream
so the streamer can do an activity
and stuff.
That's a point.
A similar system is on YouTube. That's
the leaderboard,
but they don't have channel points
[music] sadly.
They should really do channel points on
YouTube, man.
Can do so [music] much things.
Thank you for the hydrate.
I'm going to fail at this tutorial
thingy. I I I have a
I feel so tired that I don't want to
record this. I don't know. Should I
record it?
What just happened? Uh so when you
redeem it I will see it and I will do
that activity as in
um are you redeemed hydrate stretch and
posture check now that means I will have
to hydrate I will have to stretch and
correct my posture and stuff like that.
Hello you gank. Welcome.
I see you on kick. Hello. Hello.
Hello.
Not you guys. Daniel, but you your
username. Okay. You made a new name.
Okay, I'll call it.
[snorts] Hello
Hello D.
That's my real name. Ah, gotcha. Gotcha.
Ah, I see. I see.
Hello, Danielle. I'll remember that.
Okay, it's going to be 12. No, but okay.
Uh,
we knew his nickname. Got you. Got you.
Okay, I have to do this.
[snorts]
Can I wing this?
No. No. No. No. No. I have an idea. So
guys, I have an idea. I'll make a really
bad video which is so basic and so the
so hard to understand but if there's
demand [music] for people who wants to
have a clearer video clearer better
video [music] explained indepth in
detail video then I will make it that
day okay is that good enough
but quality is quality over quantity is
better Uh o
video editing is hard. I need an editor.
Okay.
Uh what is small check? Smile check is
like a reward or like a goal
where people can donate their [music]
channel points to contribute to the
goal. So in YouTube that is uh when you
YouTube they have a goal thingy for
super chats. you send a super chat or
membership or something [music]
uh
and uh it uh and once you reach the goal
the goal will be completed same system
how can I go wait I I'll turn it on
again I guess um
all right
have to like do this from plus dashboard
smile check. I was so dumb to like um
use the
uh
what do you call it? Um
okay, let me see. Power up smile check.
I'll just extend it to 31 dish. 30 days.
Okay, it should be active
2 million. [laughter] Yeah,
so much messages.
The thing is now I used to have so many
channel point stuff. Most of them were
automated.
You uh do this and it will affect the
stream model will change this and that.
I used to have so many stuff. I had to
remove so many things.
since my PC couldn't handle all these
automations and advanced [music] stuff.
Now I'm like a barebones
uh I'm like I'm like uh doing like a
normal barebones stream but everything
is basic caveman. Yeah, caveman type of
shrimp. Yeah, caveman.
>> [cough]
>> Uh, I think I have to hide this bar now.
Not sure. I think Wait one second. I
think I'll just merge all of this
together. [music]
Okay, now I'll just do this.
So, should I do the recording? I could
do it right now.
Twitch some uh subscription same as
channel member. Yes. Yes.
Uh the difference is Twitch takes 50% or
something. A lot of cut.
YouTube is cheaper. You can put like 29
rupees now. So it's so cheaper.
So, it's all good.
[cough and clears throat]
Okay. Uh, I want to do it, but also I
don't want to do it. I don't know if I
can do it.
Okay, I'm going to do it. Okay, guys.
Break this. I'm going to do this and go
sleep.
Okay.
Hi.
Uh, let me prepare all the things.
Autoactive. Okay.
What?
What is this? Why is it broken? Oi.
Refresh.
So, we need the VA embed player
and this
and I need a link to my website
v embed
where
chocolate space.
I need to put a link to this. I keep
forgetting where is that link where it's
in my phone.
I have to update my website as well.
Why is web designing hard?
But yeah, you don't need a web custom
website. You can just use link
uh like
lit link or something.
away from YouTube signing off. Okay,
take care. Good night. Good night. Good
night.
[clears throat]
Take care.
Hi,
thank you for coming by.
Lord embed.
Where
Hi.
I'm just going to do this and just wrap
up.
I'll edit it tomorrow.
Hi
So 3 2 1
go.
Hello everyone and welcome to a
technical detail video explaining about
how I did my
on how I implemented my 24hour
va
24hour channel stuff.
So in this video I will be going into
uh like a full in-depth details on how I
implemented my setup but also
um since it's this will be my first time
doing like a tutorialish [music] kind of
technical detailed video.
Um this may be rough and raw coming from
me for for now [music] but in the future
if anyone is interested on learning how
to do it and how to do use it for your
own use cases feel free to comment down
below. I will make a detailed better
tutorial on these topic in the far
future. Okay. Hi. So, let's start
with what uh So, let's start with
how I did it
and what inspired me to do this 24-hour
V setup. Right.
So
when I was scrolling through
Twitch category called always on, I
noticed like these big streamers like
Bon Peanut, Co, PewDiePie, a lot of
Stroud, a lot of streamers, they used to
showcase their
broadcast.
>> [music]
>> So, what I realized from my research is
there's two ways you can do this. Like
either you locally record your streams
[music] and buy like a cloud server
where you you upload these recorded
video content [music] and then you play
them in a loop. That's how the uh Loi
girl channel [music] and other 24-hour
music channels and stuff happen are
that's how the 24-hour channels on
YouTube works, right? So in my case,
what I would like to do is to showcase
all of my VA footage which I have on my
YouTube channel.
And I wanted in a way that it's
clear [music] that it's a it's a rerun,
it's a vaude and such. Yeah.
So what I did in the very beginning like
before uh the idea for a 24x7 channel
ever [music] happened, what I did was
for my streams, I used to have a way to
display a random VOD
from my YouTube channel whenever I'm
away from my stream whenever I'm in a
BRB
uh BRB state. So, I use Sammy to do
this.
So, this was like my first ever [music]
version or iteration of this setup where
whenever my OBS
see uh whenever my OBS scene is on
V scene or if I'm in a sleep sleeping
scene and stuff, I used to manually
put like a lay a list of my YouTube
streams which I wanted to showcase and
it randomize it randomizes this list
and [music] then it gets like a
timestamp like a random duration. So
that means this whenever I switch to a
random
uh So that means whenever I switched my
scene to void or sleeping scene on in
OBS, [music]
it would play a random YouTube video
from my YouTube channel at a randomized
time stamp. That was how the first
iteration of this setup [music]
existed.
Then
when I did my jockathon event where it
was it's a sabathon or donutathon event
where I decided to stream for 24 hours
every single day till I reached the goal
which is to get a new model to acquire
funds for the new model. So
during that jockathon event, [music] I
had instances where I had to go to sleep
and take breaks from my stream cuz I had
to be on stream for 24x
for 24 hours, right?
And be actively there. So in that
scenario,
what I did for version two was whenever
I switch to the VRV scene, it will still
copy the same setup from the first
iteration which is get a random VOD from
my whole channel.
Yeah, this time instead of manually
inputting the channel YouTube ids, video
ids, I made it so that it will fetch all
the videos in a list and then it will
fetch uh it will take a random video and
play it at a randomized time. So that's
how the [music] second iteration
worked and
in a way it is good and all but
since
[cough]
in a way it worked and all But since I
multistream on YouTube and Twitch, since
I stream on YouTube, I have to worry
about playlist.
So whatever content I am live streaming,
I have to worry about playlist. The
issue with the Joathon
uh event was I had to make a Joathon
playlist with which has all the Joathon
streams, right? But the condens
are varied and different. So this was a
one of the most
troublesome variables I had to figure
out. So what I did was
since I have to worry about the content
types and [music] playlist and I noticed
streamers who already do a 24-hour
channel setup like co
like co
streamers who do a 24-hour setup like co
here. He has like a setup where it's
literally playing a random vaude. It's
literally similar to the system I
implemented on Sammy as well, like
playing a random vault on a randomized
time. But here, as you can see, he
[music] has like a player time code
stuff and the now playing stuff,
everything, which is really, really
nice.
And I noticed something like co- uses
like YouTube V setup
as in playlist.
If I were to look at
Co's
website and he has a website called Vhat
and stuff like all of this is literally
YouTube playlist where viewers can vote.
Uh
Like when I noticed this page where this
is how the codes uh 24x7 channel runs.
So like they have like a viewer a voting
system. So all of this here is like
playlist
like all the V footage from his YouTube
channel like streams from his Twitch are
put in a playlist on YouTube uploaded to
YouTube and put in a playlist. Yeah. So
I also wanted something like this. So
after my Jokathon even ended,
I made a third version of my randomized
setup, YouTube playlist setup, which is
this is version three setup. So what it
does is it fetches all the YouTube
playlist for my YouTube channel. And
this time if I were to show a little bit
of it. Um yeah. So this time what I did
was it will check so uh it will check my
Twitch category when I'm streaming on
Twitch and YouTube and Kick. It'll check
what's my current category on [music]
Twitch. So, if I'm playing a game like
Arc Raiders and stuff, it'll
make make it so that it recognizes that
I'm playing Arc Raiders and it will
link.
I made it so that it can link playlist.
So, this in a way I had to manually do
it. As you can see over here, I had to
manually link the YouTube playlist like
this. Uh where for each game type or
category type, I had to link their
YouTube channel YouTube playlist.
So this was iteration number three or
four. I forgot the numbers. [laughter]
So, what it this does is when I'm live,
it will check what [music] category I'm
currently streaming to and then play a
stream from that category.
So, if I'm playing Arc Raiders and I'm
taking a break, it will play a VOD from
our creators playlist for my randomized
time and it'll be shown on stream like
that. So, that was version three.
And then I had an idea. I want to reuse
my it like version one and version two.
Like that was like the randomized award
thingy, right? So what I did then was
when I'm not streaming
when I'm not streaming on Twitch or
YouTube it will use the
version one setup that is it will
rand uh fetch all the YouTube streams
for my channel and then randomize it and
play from the random timestamp.
And around this period like around last
year [music]
or in 2025
I noticed YouTube embed API had made
some changes. So usually in a YouTube
embed
like the structure will be HP the
structure would be like this where
YouTube.com/mbbed
then you have to put like the main video
uh main video or you can um put a
playlist and then you have to manually
input all the videos you want to be in a
embedded playlist. But this year in
2025, I noticed that you need to have a
wait in 2035 they made some changes that
you need to have like a uh referenc
that means you have to put a website
or destination where where you are
embedding it too. It's similar to
Twitch. If you try to embed your Twitch
stream on your website, you have to type
your referencer. That's your website
address on the I frame, right? You have
to do that now for YouTube as well. And
it's such a big issue and it was such a
struggle for me. So uh I found a way I
could counter it in in my case in my use
case is since I have my website
since I have my website which is built
using web studio
and they have a YouTube component. Uh
current if you uh check my website
jognix.space space.
So, if you check my website,
jocknext.space,
you can Yeah, I'm currently live
streaming while recording this,
[laughter] but yeah, you can watch my
streams and stuff. They have a YouTube
um play uh player where you can add
[music] a YouTube uh component and add
videos, playlist and such.
where you can add um we can add like a
where you can add like a YouTube
component like this over here. Yeah,
like our YouTube component over here and
then [music]
you can like customize it and over in
the settings you can like put your
playlist and your origin. This is the
referencer I was me mentioning before
the origin. So that's my website I uh
address
and the URL etc. So this is similar to
having an embed link in OBS and playing
the embed from your browser source in
OBS. Right? So here what I did it was
but the issue was how can I use Sammy to
generate a random VA
links and then send it to web studio
since I have my website built on web
studio right. So in that case I had to
since web studio allows
since web studio allows you to
use any CMS
um CMS such as notion or any of these
over here. So what I used is notion. So
let me show you that.
So this here is my notion
page which is directly. So what it does
is it will the my web studio
So what it does is it will fetch [music]
my notion data which is this. It'll
fetch my
no it'll fetch my notion data which is
from here. Here I have the main video
ID, start time, playlist ids. These are
all the playlist ids, end time vis
visible on site, all those stuff. I
added these other properties so I can
customize it and automate it to my
liking. So whenever I uh refresh the
page in no uh in my website, it will
generate a new
it will generate the new link.
it will uh since the current version
three or I believe current version four
version
um it whenever
it generates a randomized v it will
generate it every
3 hours
or 30 minutes I can change my timing to
my liking that's how I designed my
buttons so it will um uh make generate
all these links and then uh over here it
sends it to notion over here as you can
see send to notion YouTube member player
it'll send it with all the val variables
over here it [music] will send a patch
request so every time this button is run
running on no uh Sammy it will do a
patch request to notion where it will
and new
um playlist ideas and everything. Yeah.
So coming back here I was giving you
guys like a timeline of how I got
inspired and how I implemented. Right.
So here we come to the current version
of my 24hour setup. So here as you can
see there's three big buttons over here.
So the main first button will be create
created v cycle sync the middle one.
So what it does is it will let me show
you my notion page.
So here this is the notion page YouTube
playlist word cycle. So here as you can
see every single YouTube playlist I have
on my YouTube channel will be populated
over here. Even if I make a new stream
or a new playlist whenever this created
water cycle sync button runs it will do
a full thorough check. It will what it
does basically is it will loop through
every YouTube playlist key. So it uses
the playlist ID to crossch check if
so. Yeah. Uh and since my new setup has
like a database and stuff like this, let
me show you this. So what it does is it
will save all the playlist of my channel
into some into a uh object like this.
This will be the the object keys will be
the playlist ID, the thumbnail, the URL
and the title like this. As you can see
and this data is being populated on
notion. So title will be the playlist
name, the playlist ID, the playlist URL,
the thumbnail [music]
and I added these other properties
called active and mode and has been used
in octoactive. These four properties are
really important in my new setup.
I'll explain why in a bit.
So this button basically fetches and
filters and create and this here will be
it will check whether [music] it has to
create or it has to patch. So it only
creates if it does not find any
playlist which is not there in the
current list when it fetches and if it
already finds a uh finds playlist it
will do an updation as in if [music] the
title has been changed if the thumbnail
has been changed or if [music] any
description or anything changes then it
will do a patch request and updates that
like that. Yeah. [music] So that's how
the created water cycle sync button
works. And then comes the auto active.
Autoactive and run. Basically run will
be the second execution.
The first execution will be the sync
button. So it synchronizes
everything and everything is up to date.
Right? [music] So let's talk about the
created word cycle run button. So here
what it happens is it will fetch it.
What it does it will fetch the channel
videos.
So it will do three fetches actually.
One will be a fetching of the whole
channel. This is the this is a reference
to the iteration one and two where I
fetch the whole
channel VS videos for my channel. It'll
look something [music] like this.
Um it'll look something like this. like
all thousand videos thousand plus videos
of my channel will be fetched like this
and will be properly formatted so it can
[music] be used within Sammy
and then it will
do a thing where it
um cycles through the data. For example,
uh here it will be cycling through the
notion database. Here it will uh do a
request query request to check the stuff
here in the run
button. What it does basically is it
will check for the active playlist ID
and the active mode and the playlist
title. All right. And here there's a
thing there's a logic which runs over
here that will be random versus creator
playlist.
This is this officially we are in the
territory of iteration five. I call it
version five for my YouTube VA cycle
button system.
It have introduces a created playlist
system where I can control what sort of
playlist I want the 24-hour channel what
channel to be um to be played. So I can
click on any of these playlist. So I can
click on active here and it will fetch
it will fetch the videos from the
playlist ID. So what it does here it
will fetch whatever playlist which has
the active property has as a check mark
over here. It will fetch all the videos
of that playlist. Yeah.
And then here I mentioned the mode
property right here
sequential means so whenever a new
playlist is created it always will be
created on a sequential mode that means
like in a sequence mode like one video
number part 1 2 3 like that here random
so I made it I'll talk about this in the
third button the curated word cycle
autoactive
so random will also So random mode
literally will be cycling through the
playlist but in a randomized order.
So that's basically it.
So here uh the curated playlist has
single version and uh I think single
version is what I'm currently using.
[music] I have it in a loop or
something.
Yeah.
Um yeah, as you can see, um for those
who are looking at this, you'll be super
confused what the heck is going on over
here. VA. So
[cough and clears throat]
basically, as I said before, it will
loop
through every single
videos in a playlist and put it [music]
into a variable
with a comma. So I have to format it,
right? It has to be in a formatted order
like
when we see YouTube here as you can see
uh video I video ID 1 then comma then a
video ID 2 like that right so
I formatted in a way over here like that
and
again [music] I still use the reference
I call it the fall back the randomized
the whole channel randomized setup up
that happens
whenever I have
if whenever I have the random
uh this is a proper uh this is a thing I
had over in my playlist cycle
so this is a fixed mode that means if I
don't want to use a curated playlist I
can just click on random and click take
it as active then it will only use
randomiz
What? What
if I want a sequential one? It will uh
use a sequential one. Now a question you
would be wondering is okay jock you said
I can you can create whatever playlist
you want wish to be view it for the
board channel uh for the 24-hour channel
stuff right so
what if the selected playlist which are
active runs out of videos then what
yeah so that comes the fall back so I
made it so that if
the
if the curated word. So what happens
here is all the curated videos will have
a max number of videos which can be uh
put in a uh embedded playlist. It will
be num I can set the max number of
videos minimum [music] and uh global
video count. So uh creator playlist will
always have 10 videos [music]
regardless of their size.
All curated videos will have 10. So 10
videos per channel per playlist can be
added. Then the rest will be using the
randomized.
So it will be way easier if I can show
if I show it to you uh from my website.
So here so currently as of right now
uh this is a playlist where piano
learning this playlist only has one
video. Then the next playlist will be
Battlefield and then the next playlist
will be Destiny 2. If we were to check
our notion here, it says Battlefield 4,
then [music] Destiny 2 and also piano
learning. So right. So these three
playlist are active and [music] it
fetches the videos. So those two
playlist only has one video. Then rest
of 10 videos from Destiny. So 10 videos
from Destiny is over here. Then [music]
rest from here from number 21 or
something 22 on 23 onwards. As you can
see everything else is random. [music]
And you may have noticed in iteration
five version five I add up to 90
embedded videos
and embedded playlist. So that way what
I can do is I can just run my setup
once a week so that it has enough
content to [music] be played throughout
the week. Isn't that really cool?
Yeah. Now uh comes the autoactive. Now
you'll be wondering uh Jo has to
manually change the playlist cycle,
right? But no, what I have made over
here,
what I have made over here, I don't need
to do that. I just need to run this
button once and it will
randomly randomly
it will randomly trigger
any of the playlist. Let me show you
this. It'll randomly trigger any of the
playlist. That's why here there's new
propert two new properties which has
been introduced
for the created what cycle autoactive
button that will be has been used and
autoactive. [music] So the playlist I
want it to automatically cycle through
and automatically go active and stuff. I
have to takeick it over here manually.
This is a manual process where
autoactive has to be ticked here. As you
can see the manual uh here as you can
see the random version is unticked cuz I
I can manually do this right. So here
[music] I don't want it to be automated.
Rest of all the uh YouTube playlist I
want it to be automated. So I have
ticked it autoactive. [music]
Then has been used is literally
any of these random playlist which
automatically turns into active that
property will be tech has been used. So
let's say I run currently battlefield 4
destiny 2 and piano learning is used are
active right. So those pro play three
playlists their property for has been
used will be ticked. Then when I run the
button again under another set of three
random playlist content will be active
right then
that means the the the
has been used property for the last
three playlist that won't be changed. So
that means every single time it's always
always going to be different playlist
which will be showcased
and this has been used property will
only get resetted once all of these
playlists have been
automatically played.
So once and only when all of these
streams has been these playlist has been
played at least once. So that means all
of these has been used uh playlist uh
like this property over here only when
every single item over here that's like
how many
excluding the random one once and only
when 131 playlist has everyone has been
gone like has been used check mark is
ticked
then only it will do a complete reset.
That's what I did over here. So
once um once everything has been used
then it will do a complete reset and
start over again.
Yeah. Isn't this cool? And this is such
a I know most of you still didn't get
what I was talking what I was yapping
about here but still that means every
so uh currently I'm um
so currently I have scheduled this
button to run on every Saturday if I'm
correct. Yeah, Wednesday and Saturday
was the initial one. Then I chang this
to Saturday if I'm correct.
Yeah, if I'm correct, I did change it to
Saturday. So every Saturday it will
trigger the created cycle sync button.
Then after the sync button is done, it
will do the autoactive button and then
it will run the run button over here.
Yeah. So [music] in a way I don't need
to touch my Sammy at all over my created
word player on notion. All I have to do
is sit back and relax and you guys can
enjoy
whatever content which is played
throughout the week.
But in this
setup, iteration five,
I do have wished to make some more
changes to this. Like as I said, I got
inspired by other big creators who do
who run their V channels, right? Their
24-hour channels. [music] Like for
example, my biggest inspiration going to
be Co. how he does like the timestamps,
time code over here. and also the now
playing thingy and [music] code uh co
has it where people his community can
vote
which uh rerun to be played. That's
something I also wish to have for my 24x
channel.
I feel like it's really cool that rather
than like a randomized curated playlist,
I can let my audience or you guys can
decide what type of content you want to
be played. And that's really good. And
once the uh voted content has been over,
you can I can always fall back to the
randomized condent too for the week or
maybe run another voting thingy. Yeah, I
have so much ideas in my mind for
version six and seven.
But for now, this is uh version five of
my V cycle system.
And currently
I am running this locally.
Let me show you my OBS. I'm currently
recording in the same OBS which I stream
to. But yeah, so um
I use this plug-in called branch output.
Branch output uh plugin allows me to
send my scene which is this one. This is
a browser source which shows my website.
This is how my V channel works. So the
audio from this browser source gets
broadcasted
as if you as similar to how you go live
on OBS and to YouTube, Twitch and stuff.
Here I'm sending the signal to Mel multi
meltd which allows me to multiream to
Twitch kick and other places. Here I'm
currently streaming it to Twitch and my
main channel uh as a private stream just
to do some testing and stuff for the
behind the scenes of it. And this is the
main uh 24x7 channel YouTube and the
kick one. Yeah. And [music] currently my
current setup for this is uh sending the
feed on 360p cuz again
my current setup is a local
setup. That means I have to use my PC
resources to run this 24-hour channel.
Right.
Meanwhile,
these other creators, I believe they
have their own cloud something.
Yeah, in a way, I could also do the same
thing in the future. That would mean I
would have to invest on a cloud server
[music] where I have to have the same
setup I have. Like I think I have to
have Sammy running somewhere.
>> [cough]
>> But I have to run Sammy somewhere and I
will have to run OBS as well so it can
do the thing right.
So yeah, uh in a way I won't be doing a
cloud setup right now or I think I will
only do it in the far future. If this
experiment of mine of testing this
always on 24x7 channel system,
everything [music]
see how that goes and everything. if
everything goes well, if I'm happy with
it, I would really love to switch to a
cloud setup so I don't have to worry
about it. And um
for example uh as an example I can say
[cough]
As an example, I would like to say it
will be Asmin Gold's 24x7 channel where
[music]
whenever
Asmin go is live on his main channel, I
notice his uh 24 always on channel
actually pauses the feed. Like this is
really cool and I'm getting so much
inspiration for version seven and 8.
Like [music] it also shows like a
schedule like what's going to be the
next playlist [music]
and such and like it also has like
background music and stuff. I I believe
this is running on a cloud server and
everything is done probably like
cloud-based. It's like something
automated some kind of coding behind the
scenes or something. But this is really
cool, right? Yeah. And
it it opens up a new doorway for me to
like experiment and see how other
creatives have done their setup and make
my own implementation
for it. So in in my current
implementation,
I'm happy that I'm happy with the
current setup I have currently. It is
really good.
It fits the way I want it to work.
Whatever idea I had, it works out.
But yeah, I'm excited about the future
holds in my creative [music] endeavors
in these technical things and using
Sammy and again I want to profess this
that whatever I have shown today you can
do this using streamer mix it up any
other stream streaming uh tools out
there like third party streaming um
assistant tools out there like streamer
bot I believe I could have done it way
better
with like like literally look at my com
buttons like when you look at like so
many of these blocks over here your hair
will go crazy right honestly it goes
crazy for me too since [music] I'm more
comfortable using Sammy so I'm more fine
suited for Sammy but if I were to do
this whole
in streamer. I believe I would just need
one command cuz you can use custom code
in streamer and do it. It'll be so
easier and better if you know coding.
You can implement it within streamer bot
like you can take it to the next level
too. Yeah.
But yeah, this is this has been Joex.
This was the technical details on how I
implemented my 24x7 always on channel
setup. The I call it the YouTube
playlist watch cycle system
and you currently watch the whole if you
have watched the whole thing. This is my
current version five setup of this
currently. In the future, if I ever
bring any updates and uh new new
innovations into this current setup, I
would love to share it to you guys. Hi.
And also before I end this video, I
would like to say that
I did rubbish over and skip skim over
some technical
informations on how I fetch my stuff. I
believe I can't say that out loud on
YouTube. YouTube might not like it.
[laughter]
There's multiple ways you can fetch your
video ids through API or other ways. CLI
both methods are there. So yeah, you can
do that. You can do any of these on
Sammy or streamer.
It's up to you. And again, [music] you
don't need to do any of these as well.
It's all good. And if you are someone
who wish to go with the other method
which is cloud-based where you input
recorded content manually and like I
just did on a dashboard you can do that
believe you have to pay for those
services and such but here I wanted more
control and more refined refinement in
my system so that's why I implemented
everything in Sammy and streamer bot not
streamer bot yeah Sammy and like that's
why I implemented all of this in Sammy
web studio to notion like that system.
Hi, hope you enjoyed my uh technical
details kind of uh like confusingish
tutorialish thingy. Hi, if you liked it,
do a comment down below. If you didn't
understand at all, it's totally fine.
You don't have to worry about it. If
you're curious and interested
and want to learn more about these, feel
free to let me know in the comments
section below [music]
and I would love to talk in depth. Yap
about how I do these stuff.
Hi, that's about it. This was Jockn.
Bye-bye.
Holy lord, that was so much. Oh my god.
I feel like I went all around and made
it so confusing and stuff in between.
Holy lord.
I think I went around saying cycles in
between. That's something I shouldn't
have done.
But hey, it works,
right?
It works. I show like a technical and
everything.
Oh, I was playing the watch. Frick. I
have to fix that. [music] Ah, I have to
fix that. I have to fix that. Oh, boy. I
have to fix that. No. Shoot.
Shoot.
Wait.
[cough] Wait.
No. Don't do this to me.
Oh [\h__\h] No. Uh, it's fine. It's fine. I
have the what track, right? Yeah, it'll
be fine. It'll be fine. [music] If it
it's not fine, I'll just re-record the
whole thing.
But yeah, I'll do this later.
Ah, thank you. Uh, thank you for the
raid,
Luna Moon official. Welcome,
welcome, welcome. Thank you for the
raid. Hello
I was literally about to wrap up.
Yeah. Hello, welcome in raiders. My name
is Dark Next. I'm an Indian YouTuber.
Previously, I video on how I made my uh
24x7 channel stuff.
So, yeah, I was like recording it. I was
editing it. Now I'm so tired. Uh since I
just
um made like a whole in-depth tutorial
which is so technical that no one's
going to understand.
Oh yeah. Hello. Welcome welcome welcome
welcome one second.
Hold
up. Let me
fix something.
The raid was brought to you by raid
pools. GG. Oh,
hello Luna. Thank you for the rain.
Sorry for It's okay. No worries.
No worries.
How was your stream? Hope you had a fun
stream.
Hello
I hope you have fun stream. What did you
stream today?
What did you stream? Oh, is that Blender
Unity stuff? Oh,
that is so cool.
I was just uh
scrolling through your channel.
That is so nice. Oh, you were playing a
game.
Oh, wait. That was via chat. My bad.
Wait. Oh, wait. My Oh, wait. Oh, you you
do real chat stuff. So, go on.
Nice.
Thank you for following. Thank you.
Oh my god, I talk so I y so much my
throat is dead. [laughter]
I'm already sick. I've made my made
myself more sher. [laughter]
Nice.
But yeah. Okay, one second.
I use a site that calculated you of your
best to rate and how what it does with I
don't know. H Oh, wait. I remember
signing up for that site rateful thingy,
right? I I remember that. Oh, yeah. I
remember signing up for that website.
I haven't used it. It's been a while. I
I randomly came to know about it from
Twitter.
Yeah. Yeah. Twitter, I think. Yeah.
And I think I made an account there.
That's what I
wow.
It actually calculated
me recommended you to read me. That is
so cool.
Wow.
And the website is kind of cool.
[clears throat] I did some work on my
new world I'm working on and some
outlast trials. Oh, nice. Nice.
That is nice.
[clears throat]
Let's go.
I haven't dabbled into uh via chating
stuff.
Um but that is cool. I would love to
make
everything cuz I plan to do like uh
concerts and stuff. So I would need to
learn Unity or Unreal on like 3D stuff.
Ah, so much.
But that is really cool though, you
know, to make Vader walls. Really cool.
That's nice.
[laughter]
Excuse me.
Uh, I'm eating some water. Hydrate
everyone.
Our
Last Trials. What is that? Is it a game?
Our Last Trials.
Oh, it's a game.
Oh,
it's still in beta or something. I got a
mail from though. It is still in beta. M
cool.
This is nice.
Raid pools.
That's nice.
Sh.
I'll I'll have to check out your channel
as well.
Whenever I'm free, I'll drop by if I'm
able to catch you live. Hi.
Um, [clears throat]
so yeah, I think I'll have to edit the
video I just right now record it
tomorrow.
So it
go I went in depth. I feel like no one
will get it, but
could you ever do a singing stream
again? Uh
someday there
maybe this month. Yeah, I can do it.
Yeah, maybe this month I can do it.
Yeah,
sure. Yeah,
also we faced a lot of bugs today. I'll
have to fix my [music] back end.
Let me unblock all the but this thing
[laughter]
I had to wait I think I can just click
on unblock. Yeah.
No let [music] the errors pop in. I'll
just fix them off stream.
So yeah. Oh yeah. Dealish. Were you
watching the uh the segment where I was
record live recording the technical
details thingy?
Uh if you did what how would you rate
it?
How would you how would you rate my
tutorial?
Another game I want to call out. You can
always DM me.
Oh, yeah. Sure. Sure. Okay. Outlast
trials. No, my child.
I have to buy it, I guess.
Man, don't tell me it's a horror game.
Oh god, it's a horror game.
Okay, I need to buy this. Can you redo
it? No.
Okay, I recorded it for um
it's a 47 minute video. Holy lord,
it's a 47 minute video. Oh god. Wait. Uh
I think you can hear it from a
background. New music. Wait one second.
So I recorded the multitrack thingy. So
both the
both the uh uh avatar only audio version
and the
uh if I can change the track to this the
I also recorded the display capture
thingy as well
if I'm correct.
Yeah.
So, I'll have to I think I have to um
since it's a Oh god, the errors are
coming. Since it's a multi-track video
recording, no. Oh, I just closed my
background music. Oh my god. Wait, wait,
wait.
Yeah, since it's a multitrack video, uh
I have to buy I have to get the Oh my
god, what I'm doing? I have to get the
nuty
thingy, right? This thing.
Where is [\h__\h] He released it yesterday
over this one. Wait. No. No. Wait. Where
is it?
Multitrack
video demixer script. Yeah. So, I have
to download this.
It will convert into two separate videos
or something. Then I can put it in
Dainci and then I can edit it. Yeah.
What are you making? So, we uh so I made
like a tutorial on how I made my 24x7
channel. Uh wait, let me check my OBS.
Is it live?
Yeah, it's live. Okay, so I have my 24x7
channel. It's on Twitch as well.
Uh Jox247
and
so hello Bacon, [clears throat]
welcome.
I was currently playing a older reward.
So I was giving like uh I so I today I
recorded like two videos. Um
that's why I recorded two videos. Don't
mind the scuff. I'm showing my whole
screen which is bad. But yeah, don't
mind the scuff. But hold one second.
Hold up. Don't mind the scuff.
Wait. Uh so I finished recording the
introduction like why I made the channel
and what you can expect about it etc.
It's a 6 minute video short one. Then I
just the errors. Then I made the
technical details version. So if anyone
who's tech nerdy who's interested how I
made it so they can like refer it. I
made it. It's my first time ever making
like a tutorial. So, I thought I'll make
it in a rough manner like a skim through
the like crucial crucial details or like
the actual technical things like using
YouTube DLP to fetch all the videos
channel and uh then make like a
database system like I made over here.
So it fetches the channel then make it
into an object with a playlist ID. Then
this goes into notion then it uh does
the thing over here like that
much to ultimate is still in a panel
maybe. Oh yeah yeah I have to remove
that. Yeah thank you.
So, I don't know if it's a good video
though, but yeah. So, basically, uh,
TLDDR, since you're new here, Lunasa,
so well, let me find it. Oh god, where
are you? Where are you? Okay, so
basically, I have a thing. Um,
this idea developed over time when I was
streaming. So I used to take like 5 to
10 minutes to come back to my stream
like if I'm going to eat dinner or
something something. No. So I thought
isn't it better if I could play some
random clips or vod like pre like past
streams from my YouTube channel to be to
be shown when I switched to my BRB scene
and OBS. Yeah. So the idea developed
from there to the point that I wanted to
showcase a random vote at a random time
stamp. Then it developed from there to
the point that um
it will check what is my category on
Twitch for example just chatting. So it
will play
uh a video or like a a video from my
playlist. The just chatting playlist. I
have a playlist. I believe I have a just
chatting playlist or Yeah. So this one.
[laughter]
So it will play videos from this.
Checking my current Twitch category and
stuff. Then it again I got inspiration.
Then I was like, okay, these big
streamers are having like a always on
thingy and this always on Twitch
category is really cool. I want to do
something like this. So I started to
research how they did this setup,
especially like Co over here, Coalition
Gaming. Really, uh, it was good to like
look up how he made his stuff,
everything.
So yeah, that's how I made it. So
everything works uh in Sammy. I think
you can do this in Streamer. Mix it up
if you ever use those uh other tools out
there. Yeah, it's basically easy.
[laughter]
So not easy, but it's a bit complicated,
but yeah. [laughter]
So my setup works with the three button
thingy.
It's a fully automated. I don't have to
touch anything. Every Saturday new play
uh created playlist gets selected and
automatically be made. So this week uh
is Battlefield 4, Destiny 2 and piano
learning.
Uh piano learning, right? Yeah, piano
learning. So yeah, next week uh God
knows what's next.
So, I made a short video on that. Also,
I need to change one of my buttons.
Uh,
this is a sat Saturday trigger. No.
Yeah. So, I'm not changing it every
Wednesday, Saturday. It's going to be
Saturday only.
Hi.
Oh my god.
Damn.
Like that. My V channel V always on
setup is done.
YouTube backend system is also done. Now
what's left for me to work on is the
user unified user system. No. So people
from YouTube, Twitch, Kick, you'll have
your own user accounts
which looks like this. Uh wait,
which looks like this. You'll have your
own UID.
Public UID will be 1 2 3 4 like that.
uh like that.
And then this will help me to make chat
log system like improve my
current chat log system I have.
And uh same with events as well.
H where is it?
Yeah. Uh chat loics system and the event
system. I need to upgrade those two.
These are current currently version one
setup.
I have to upgrade this show.
What's what was the first ever channel
you watched on Twitch? That's a good
question. Uh
actually don't know.
Is there a way to check it? I don't
think it's possible to check it. Uh
I think it will be probably something
from the browse
or like when I opened Twitch for the
first time in 201
17, no 2018. 2018 is the day I
discovered about Twitch
and stuff. I was like watching YouTubers
on YouTube
like watching those vlog
videos this and that. Then I discovered
what this this platform called Twitch.
Then I think I watch someone from here.
I remember watching like Fortnite
streamers and stuff
once.
So then yeah.
Yeah. Then then my uh
um stuff changed. I think I started to
watch
uh streamers. Oh yeah, I remember Tyler
one l I remember watching him though I
don't I don't watch League but I just
watched I remember seeing some clips of
him. I remember that. I remember the
first Japanese YouTuber I watched it was
[\h__\h]
I still remember her. I was like looking
at uh Japanese streams and YouTuber with
the VTuber tag. I didn't even know that
this was a VTuber
until
after four or five months on YouTube, I
discovered Kizuna Eye.
Then I was like, "Oh, wait.
>> So this is a VTuber
like that."
Yeah, that's how I stumble across [\h__\h]
Look at it sound is cool.
But the language better know Japanese I
know I have to patch up my Japanese man.
[clears throat]
So done.
So many things.
I'm dying.
Oh, there's an ad break on Twitch.
I'll have to wrap up for today.
I'm so tired. Oh, yeah. I was supposed
to show these on the video. I forgot
like how much is it for cloud cloud OBS
server and everything. Ah,
no.
I forgot. No,
these t are so expensive, man. Like
look at this. Uh
OBS it's like
$20. No, not 20. I don't think it's 20.
You have to pay for other apps as well.
Right.
So, I feel like
uh Andy Scuff is better if I'm doing
like a cloud or be stuff, but I have to
pay $90 a month. That's crazy. That's
like how much in my currency?
8,000 rupees. Hello.
I can do so much with that money.
Oh yeah.
God, I feel a little bit sick. Oh god.
I'll take some rest.
Where did you find that dollar?
Come on.
Well, uh oh yeah, the world shot. If you
have any ideas where I could improve the
V system, do let me know. Okay,
you have any other ideas or something? I
would totally love to like
spend time to
build it and Sammy and stuff.
That'll be nice.
Ad break is over. Yep. Finally.
Welcome back.
Well, honestly speaking, I only have one
month left. That's March before I go to
Japan. So, I have to fully finish the
watch system and an automated system
where
uh like once I'm not in my house, right,
I can just tell my family to just turn
on my PC on a something then I can
somehow
um I think it's possible to do wake on
land
publicly without being on a kind of a
local server local network. So if I'm in
a different country, I can just click on
a button like uh send a magic my phone
or something. It can turn on my PC from
India. Maybe if that's possible and you
have to research into that. If that is
possible, man, I'm going to do it.
I have to do it. Then I can like
automatically shut down, start up
everything, right? All those stuff.
since I have to locally run this setup,
right?
So,
yeah, then I have to finish the user map
system. I'll tomorrow I'm not sure if
I'm streaming. I just have like a
meeting to attend to.
Also, this month we will be doing video
content, more shots and more videos. I
have to do that. I am kind of
brainstorming what I want to do and
everything. Then my new then the new
model stuff uh that's going to be
happening. I don't know probably this
month or no not this month probably next
month. I I'll video when [laughter]
a vlog and stuff will happen from Japan
I guess. Yeah. I have to edit learn how
to edit properly.
Yeah. Yeah.
Then the thing is now since I'm more
technical when it comes to the stream
stuff and everything, I would love to do
automations and would love to do OBS
stuff and everything. You know, I'm like
thinking I'm going to be having my model
reveal stuff happening soon since I paid
for the license. I finally have I can
own my IP finally
uh for the model and everything for this
year. Uh, so I was like,
I would love it if I can make a totally
unique
the immortal PNG reveals thingy fully
automated like
but the thing is
there's like a lot of pros and cons on
that.
So, I thought I'll just do like a normal
normal
short
10 minute 20 minute stream and then say
my thank you and just call it a day or
something. [laughter and gasps] I don't
know.
But honestly though, if I were to debut
my model and stuff now, I would love to
do some crazy
shenanigans using Sammy or Streamabboard
or using OBS in general.
It would be so cool to do stuff.
Yeah.
Nowadays,
everyone has their own unique thing they
bring, right, when they do these debut
streams. Hello, Kentosaki.
Hello. Wait, are you chatting on
my main? Oh, yeah. You are chatting on
my main. Hello.
Welcome.
Hello.
Okay. Okay. We'll we'll we can wrap up
soon. Okay.
Right.
Uh
once again, thank you Luna Moon
officials. Thank you for the read on
Twitch. It really means a lot.
Thank you for discovering me through the
raid polls uh website.
[clears throat] I'm glad I recommended
you to raid me. But yeah, thank you.
So, I'm going to be wrapping it up for
today.
But yeah, uh I'll take up your offer
once when I get last uh Outlast trials.
I'll DM me you so we can collab.
It'll be fun.
I haven't done collabs in a long while.
I miss doing collabs. So then
yeah, this year has been rough for me.
Not rough, but yeah, too busy.
So I miss doing collage. But yeah, this
is my only month, right, left.
I could take my time to like focus on
stream and other stuff, right? I think I
should do more collabs, man.
Whatever I wish to do, I'll just do it.
Have fun.
Yeah.
All right. Okay. Uh,
honestly, when you do all these
technical things, it's sometimes you
feel like you don't want to stream at
all because to start up a stream, you
have to set up so much stuff. Even if
you have like a one but button
automation, if something crashes, it
breaks your hardware. That's what
happened today. like so many crashes
like like today's YouTube stream this
today's this current stream
the data for the stream like the
data as in let me show you
right
the data for today's stream as in this
one
this this this something went wrong
somewhere and
I want to just cry. Don't mind all of
this. But yeah, like all the data for
today's stream,
this one right horizontal
all the data for today's stream from
YouTube.
Something broke somewhere
and
Yeah, it messed up my Discord events.
It messed up my announcement
and it messed up the notifier. So many
things.
And tomorrow I think I'll just sit down
and try to find the issue and fix it. So
yeah.
Oh yeah. When I end stream, I have to
make it so it automatically rates my war
uh always on channel, right?
Ah, so much work.
So much work.
So much work. Also, how do you raid on
kick?
I never figured that out.
Wait, how do you rate on cake though?
I can't do it. Weird. Okay. Anyway,
we'll be wrapping it up over here.
Take a moment to thank everyone who
lurked,
was here, who chatted today. Thank you
to everyone who came by today. It really
means a lot. I'm back from my vacation.
I will try my best to be more active.
Uh, hope you enjoyed today's stream. I'm
sorry for the low energy, by the way.
I'm so tired. It's literally 1:30. It's
going to be 1:30 a.m.
Uh, but yeah, [clears throat] thank you
again, Mina,
for being here. It really means a lot.
If you enjoy the stream,
feel free to come by the future streams
as well. Okay.
Bye. So, we'll wrap it up. Thank you to
everyone who came by today.
Thank you.
I'll see you all in the next stream.
That's going to be uh the next stream.
I'll announce it. Don't worry. I still
have to do the Fortnite stream. I have
to do arc raers. We got to grind our
crers. We got to do blue protocol.
So much stuff, bro. So much stuff.
But yeah, thank you to all who came by
again. I'll see you guys in the next
one.
Hi
ma.
I'll send you to my always on channel.
Okay. Hi, enjoy.